[{"topicId":"19","id":"19000","langCode":"vi","question":"RZi0BUNs1CQHdUO+feFdQ/+H7XoD7PyawYt84ZBwAC4fbbvEGGmiR/PY/rPXnohWVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["wouldn’t get","won’t get","get","would get"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzgTMx1k9u5xTl9Et5sdm+oxIpYcU8xOaK7HrGz71+En9sGXgvlfv3EI+DP+JzM1o0tWJMCICCREg2gw9W0f4zQg265EjrjWU3GOTKgyRCi+GTSMbHEWhfIIRDlxeXtMhZffSbUH0M9JsDNdqcq9Tt5wgB6WnkFzyctBcQMHWfUGRt9lHtWvwW1xLZRUuaDf8CtTk+Ecjq+uci5DhqzSzL2T/+DP28VpQnQL7pY9dLN1NnsM1aFmjU14QjLCJ0MQCDQfTNa6ak089bDtNcHF6UyVe/WHmXus/Hilj/e1Y3KGpJAEBCqyFcUc4Uxw9XY7z6PKnMKrDCiTPf6AbPMRdMiL5etZB2nTs5JBb0SupOr10R9qT9iS3xItT8++g3TmEM0d9TX9IeL8xCV1j0YhIZzlLATK1w0JlkeFNJtvvlQVRSfFLBNQ7wzROZdMuno4ZO6D1V9BsNKVF4braXaUzn1MWRqZpG0LaLOkUtlAgM2Mds5Run9px0HTLxNMKYbCT/rn7T68uGIJ8u5Sdd3fuO45aKnSgBvmvxpWVKwaIbhrOXyWD2V3YNlWsJSOqT3xN/qwgf6D3QKp8i1VOIwLoC1FQDqZaUTZ3DwF4IDYQbTT"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19001","langCode":"vi","question":"B8PhyHRLwW9a00E43jJfxyXUZHagar3uzx4NwKFCXOLSaz1JwhqOCG1x8PT3S+9eUuZsi7ArckZJbn77P+GJ0A\u003d\u003d","answers":["will go","go","would go","wouldn’t go"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7YVAdzTQzmun+oQSW8qq4ZN8pEzIbFCRINhf2mRvbYkp6JXLe+VWLwsqRnMIbbnMs1kH+g9nArSNVSNH6otQgStrBita93xTLdERqyRe7+tICb3syoJcKoplHNSM2oGxZHXa4rVD1mF/NPWTCCG2nHTel4/ALOkqaJr0/TFG/e+rXQwYRNaSnoG99M8ZiXOWIoiN/UH7dS/u1Xb5HufpOkgqH8ixXrvwV/jAU0ok6WRL18C322iRr2kvUyU+zXoB1m0VbKITt149cPMIQGjFDTrA3K9bY8mm3FSHMq0WDwIRv7DZYy9NhY56ykUC5Ypv/p25uMgEqHdamZyMKxmcKXLifb/LKK2OM6vwTNfPi3+X6QAHPSBGnYWfq1h0EBpRsxlEtW3yi31mzGXFSZs+YTNb7y+98m14HxDpViZHuejwF6vri1yR6cMC1lJY0C7tXWEUsaloI4zC7RfOwuEk/HB9+L5oqHw3zuffNSfZIakv8OKf9Lz8H7kKeUsKXgTPL0E5usrE77CrzBPQ+mtGdi6BiuAiY3LNFyrbF0QirnXI9LGoWoqE0b5z1NBwjhDag\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19002","langCode":"vi","question":"6PCXFF7c5aIcocQgzvO+lE2keQ3iuWmnZmV5iczLYbJTscemgquoZymFM3C6Cfv5ptOuYKJGucTxyiiH1AOv85aJV06uAMVLd+/jPiw5kTo\u003d","answers":["had to","will have to","would have to","would have had to"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzIDvN8bS5tYtpyTzFOurqDsB7vN/FAQQqUlgPiqL5HP2xAKsLbiugrPkv+KT3CZzXaiMgbpKOCvD9ShK8sKdJq2UhP4iv31fckH6ogMwAM/ralzNbTvcRlj0K2dmPhe5e6FaSGsVp59cYYn/osG93g1HJ1bYtV0S+gqt1YRrVynsnIsFft7z+yTqjc/md+rxiZNf+RXWc5FrYYFjb4Dvgk9IKqEjAAz4Ak8Fzcx88R+DVl6t1C2azKY4kgdLdzV0QhaiT1L4RnuRERxNeV3ahX8emV8MC7KnMxO55koPQ2yXwvpT9cAzV02t/IiCF8Zso/dklWhAMyIPpoTnbBFivXprVMNUqWPkG6RJVVogWpVGrK9F/kKQ7n+4AExPofwMyoSornYi7cOcMZY2AuziIJXtVA7agLrmZRwdAdDF1Grh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8VlnvzrpvCCOYCVY4h7pMhUjeDgjbwCKK6JxCAdKGLNYM1/OpBQPExwN9uU++brO9e+n3jyIb+/slLAOvNS7NNDQx6grbS8H56KbXXYSBaViSCfDJUeRAHnhMS5ZfeCGHYEGmofQiiqLUYk+RaMv477rIj+zjzEf07GtB39S2V5JXUXsWaog3lZNIRWpopmUCU\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19003","langCode":"vi","question":"WXCfbdSUj2CA9nQwaL2sz8Nh0MXVNJeArww/ILO+hEzs9WR/zr8JmUw++x4kJI4RVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["shouldn’t wear","wouldn’t have  worn","should wear","would have worn"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6kXVlb3Gd65lFcPwgMHV+DFDg1Mq6P+fZrCAzGE6kVD2xAKsLbiugrPkv+KT3CZzXaiMgbpKOCvD9ShK8sKdJq2UhP4iv31fckH6ogMwAM/ralzNbTvcRlj0K2dmPhe5e6FaSGsVp59cYYn/osG93g1HJ1bYtV0S+gqt1YRrVynsnIsFft7z+yTqjc/md+rxiZNf+RXWc5FrYYFjb4Dvgk9IKqEjAAz4Ak8Fzcx88R+DVl6t1C2azKY4kgdLdzV0QhaiT1L4RnuRERxNeV3ahX8emV8MC7KnMxO55koPQ2yXwvpT9cAzV02t/IiCF8ZsjBaik3Q40mpAeYt+tEC8GrCTJuhI/XD/SXhhjxnH0jCHLD1oqIIVpI1+x3tHzB7zMPbGOGFz3zHxe3nj5R6BD/JjH3xxOfMGACj/ZnBHJBApS6qRXgfdlF/vDbIekInPhlHWdmJAl66S4iXtBgIdRiwoEtf4D5vTP2u66fUYsK+E8YdxmwvfluAvSZ7/i64ZrRA+J5VoNri6ZXX3Pxt9aXdK8A58ATte/PkEOdvHlfMjsnVTanT3ulZGPzFUArvksiyHx+v5SPu9RpsoNwrTtBpS+i/Rsunn4wJ7tM/5afz15kp7qQ80seNXesG5HQgur/YPr5PWr/OuGW4m6nlhsq++5wFizfJzh9/caQim34BUnXiHTQ3j4j3FKG4aeyCgbrmo2Hsslx9zwVOT8fMDIQ8b4PXA2t54L9uJbpmcSbfOuTrPcCApa8PiRzyFp2cOr2rUdBnGRPTd1qJquzcU22xNz1ajPkIseVg9jOGDqylF8WhaVts0sFqNTibSqVPsaCT7/DhUw+X+K+/Rsz190dErqEwRVU/vyAeExo77B0eg+f389fvN5MaqVtvol0lfBbZnSosg20xriM7yJLygGQ1OvjRXJMAfMz5ncop0GD5nnE2+52TmU2kSiZsUyOJ3TVniEteihg6xkAFFhtI8pcb7/T3oYCA+1Cpx+knmsSK"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19004","langCode":"vi","question":"yRZEedGaREPh3SpBdrZ9NJBV1RlW7JRQLDfiENR48WsBqrdOoFlw3o72dqkTwbRB","answers":["may lose","would have lost","may not lose","wouldn’t lose"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzY74p96ACwQ90PYV5B25i6/y9XEZ24vn7wSkmnQBUE9JLUk5IEKbSy38/hrmX6JpFMrjmME+ne79T+OBmbJHqIelCkjKDxtEzq0KOc34pXFkWy14dZVcq79hqUqZCa9zu4ZmsrPP1qolVqba0dTKhTnxJRB3JtJXSz8M2JbQt/TT5+pcCNmy1Wy1KWo8nyeCNmz1L6t2OTYeIEGt80J0QbzMQ2ejwLGYiEUrCVdINwo362bW+X4zGKJzbAE2ZUYTyLSqIqX0ckPYb/kXy2wOYodYjlDYdyWj0crrB4QhTuENYvaLfEOo2GvtMUwe0ZKPi+ALJRZzO8rW/GwMHJSV/sK9r9NePG+YAmV5LQX7/3kIty+R7kIB/DZT8g8bEuNiSASuguxQspsfDK8v4kwy0EhKykmqLkEaCOscX6F9tmJiDvrlv6fIOkQJbWLcl446pGcCKGvwKUiJ/NKIcmfi7NlhvVp4SeVD50BL3x8zDzzEyN8wH4nF+VyHorBUJeaItWyU8fZQG+RvfzOrRK9QvwZy5yDnWy/UE0903Ge2HZZpNsuKTOprK6Wh5mmcbSooEBoJdkr/CM+4Qi/FHdNPBiNt/GsFbGIUDtqtNvz6eTTwHtXnf+0MEnbBcAGhYtsPlP/BtZ8NLXNbgwvv5SFp8MOcQWT6pd4kXSb9NvxSYaF1o0MqlI5S3AGwZWbOT7vqdVHmtb/lyQTOm7iiaJZFp3YuLgRKH3ECOi+0tLYo9GkFy0O+u0ECKoACGu27tFyOslGbHsz8/arAYerwWpS/15wfMWnOOH9ywDaeeaUwKxQntipLMHIdQCr94W71xDW/7wHCqDkJde4OdcFL8OumSCC8WIMwtwgIeIwjHhq7EwgFYrM9dF3xT2oUiDldPB7Kgaza8BpJ2VNi7DMH1GEpnVW0PKiJbgeOkooHpho2oAu+UC24v5KVdGq2ORWm6u2woO0b03ZjjIo8zoZhuxMh+TWPH2vx2THocBWWWCDf2nWZUGMCjVkOwClinqAKjtihWyARL46NpRZQLhauZQpUvg\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19005","langCode":"vi","question":"PZsAP09t6w2P6lR+f9QXaovVhAZq8MudXzQTEWweRwt0s6B0O+6RnAKPBo4ovLrMvCZpl9EWDxjqVeMa3akBwg\u003d\u003d","answers":["won’t come","would come","will come","would have come"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeExIbMexcvidbfWkigM/eyyk8Jc2+kVSDig+vKwm0DYlzbWg/O9hTSfSjLCgZSyeGDsUXjOv4beG70KLFZZeDutyvTRZ8qJSjPd4BTXbXuVjtsEBKyV+ejBtArdcbDHv27JqXT9tctyg9r3MXbpdXG99qgG1y8tVGN6YlzJgHZYRHet6xkofN2phfe+W0fSyQuHEZUGa/9s+/hdxjiV1PHLjx16yKyPDLPfm6ZjXPvnILjAA96JCWZoW5gAtnHmlKiooo4fw5p0mw1EE4+beitcrOwQseJXitZnEkKfVfaOzRUxBtcVTo62t/19whYSNCRyKkrUA9kS6mZB4fOwol4oKpXG6KorSwykFWaGus4NIC0hFNocHNFaxA2ACXmGDpZnYmA0zFyidq5IwooxtCxW1VyMNX21wzDBX7wKxB7ehuEKhUjgxYaCX43AVH3+29ARll+ijAJe+juitIA+vUc402NVje20qFComXiIhQ0hIdc5CPtV1pFjSPeZi4SXxP7njLkdq7H6Al+zocKBA3Wz9oCgpn07u+gdrIK96QrbXt/+MqSaiO/M+w4u4ux4sK9rilN6nHgRofHah5f9VXFjmdJv0UAvnHhKyi8NB8STmgnW+tX5/x6kWp1dp9X6kNNQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19006","langCode":"vi","question":"1Q599dD2vcH2KJwtubKejNuk+UryoaEivhI1RuSzx7RFt/Wm0xHstSQuAKIvM7vT+YVAnUkqTm2IKrdFupQeag\u003d\u003d","answers":["would have been","be","would be","will be"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE054Ow96ZlPi7422GpC08YRwp5PMMna10cAs62xZBGN7p6JXLe+VWLwsqRnMIbbnMs1kH+g9nArSNVSNH6otQgStrBita93xTLdERqyRe7+tICb3syoJcKoplHNSM2oGxZHXa4rVD1mF/NPWTCCG2nHTel4/ALOkqaJr0/TFG/e+rXQwYRNaSnoG99M8ZiXOWIoiN/UH7dS/u1Xb5HufpOkgqH8ixXrvwV/jAU0ok6WRL18C322iRr2kvUyU+zXoB1m0VbKITt149cPMIQGjFDTrA3K9bY8mm3FSHMq0WDwIRv7DZYy9NhY56ykUC5Ypv/p25uMgEqHdamZyMKxmcKXLifb/LKK2OM6vwTNfPi3+X6QAHPSBGnYWfq1h0EBpRsxlEtW3yi31mzGXFSZs+YTNb7y+98m14HxDpViZHuejwF6vri1yR6cMC1lJY0C7tXWEUsaloI4zC7RfOwuEk/GcTFyxHgn7s6s3jusrhSdVkP2JMpuWorPTSYkA+kK3EcOBBLv4WTSV/JfLV4FcSswpCAd4DLMCwRIk+B3PC1l6tu9aV1V8FkVrGtUza36QIA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19007","langCode":"vi","question":"EhC7ClhnGCoBuyU+gqW+eFRYctyyJ4Vj1jfdPL1NDtbjsuVtg1cSAKSbr1OdEfrJ","answers":["would come","wouldn’t come","would have come","comes"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8Y9kx+wTsh7l2l3JYo80gG69gTJW73PJ4t982auUFKpm4EkEHD6wq4Gi6BCQgjIAHJKGK+viciqa9nNw2Mdp3mP/p5GiH/Wr09jp/pAFObKEOQBpWBwSqsZyVY77ZbKRubZ1+QEuJgBasNWMflvR2CtSIiF51Mywt5fsLuZm6tk6UH8n5W2zFBumbHqFm+ppMU+Zh+mQg+rYfWWg8+gQqXrX9rIj/9aiiDJTSDEmpjL/1yXPbOOMER/nRBqVYhOkaXHivv0PMcqH6kanW9uFUU7MRAPX2sSNqsUITQtczwB34XquhpgglfNvbYe/yDaUDbNRcXfCXmGwZok4NE5UheF6fGlUUySrFB+zCrQknexralzNbTvcRlj0K2dmPhe5SOdmiBlWiCAqPYMt3Kctz52XSgjGq2CV7PfDs9CKLzgVP4HH4weo/vlVroXYJL0whw6HdFDEEY3PB0jXQ4BT2YPUA0trPI0yqgQH8TdAXwG4QbrNHzR6TnlMdwlseVFVzfPbfMi6U1c9VjXXpy4nafNwT42A9eLw9ks78coySTLux89K41QW+cWV76cbdZltbLYcVwbf+ydSGLEig9jVdUGUAXTtdtnoxbMR1zFdlRYFBjfzIyWiy126CVCOIulPmxujFl7COWpf9FJPAtWzPXYNjpvJRsXYrmnLs8kkhdvSNWWrnGpi6d3JtNCpOEbS62yjCEMScUlZz2BgFilwnH4eW0uHRqzmE3MGoEPG+lfE7po7z9iogzZHMDvJOnecO0tzPpZsb4cBBW57mDZe68/QSfC6Fv4hVt4s/2KK4DZdlLwM/lwTHSu5rQb/ytW1Vd4SaxI8QYGRXte3LHPGEU\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19008","langCode":"vi","question":"UENH0ePp3cf8yX7pXXJ/9vczf7BGubAe+WkOLS7GpGFuM1Rl/GwQGgrSstPKJxDz","answers":["wouldn’t spend","would spend","would have spent","spends"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE194dGaFyi7eFdoIT1RLolRN8pEzIbFCRINhf2mRvbYkp6JXLe+VWLwsqRnMIbbnMs1kH+g9nArSNVSNH6otQgStrBita93xTLdERqyRe7+tICb3syoJcKoplHNSM2oGxZHXa4rVD1mF/NPWTCCG2nHTel4/ALOkqaJr0/TFG/e+rXQwYRNaSnoG99M8ZiXOWIoiN/UH7dS/u1Xb5HufpOkgqH8ixXrvwV/jAU0ok6WRL18C322iRr2kvUyU+zXoB1m0VbKITt149cPMIQGjFDTrA3K9bY8mm3FSHMq0WDwIjAe69SOd6aZ10QdPXmH+wL0ZYkxBHUFlqC/OfEy3nFfprx5FwBWKZVe9Xb5Ifv9rKJUVYK8U++Y1gZsacvpIPKXdVpfRWHKEgk17ThqvNJ7ysFBjMwhPvknnvshTXjb2+c29ahKxkBhjLNLtjMWpui5w1SlXWn+C089AMwxh0nYyDAmHrWm0uVcXrrXdlv9kn5qzjz0pwZVdl0w1pbCOsFuO9yfcDCVdrr5qBv/EqGRTOXaU8iG3Tvqp66NttqMH6TNiLUp5Hx1AqCWxzmh1uWGdSTEiQivcdbhq+PS/44OTkmmDHaTTVnlRuq94OiX1zn/bUGjHKLoCKQWAzPxjs1RG8iwuObfPKOU/xLDECKMlJvQgOAGoksJO+MV7umzX9/QKNyVZC06g7y2F4bD95bF/omZJ3Em+uyTu+nkUtjARRzGSSS4qN/mvMG4SZYHXmT9yMkh0F6sN0jcPebC2S9ucwXibQ75xmpT5Hdw1CKxMR5jDLzcEVkJGF9L/cWxgH/z+vHYT0YIU7nfW0Jynhg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19009","langCode":"vi","question":"5aFvhsyVZNstHLDZXj3KD7TK3oAppEPbu4XT3YvWSMstJ+ckzAzLpuReQbgSr0KGT7vnHOcmEb2eBjt2+kV4dCKCmqG5sCs+z6xbO8RtnbE\u003d","answers":["would buy","bought","buy","will buy"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE24gjl71hT8X4+Owzu39k8uaPn8FtvSTgj0lKym/NOTP7oiH2qCeUuxIpd+jn5iTSQhIEHo7RrwGdTM2+4BMzXwrfiJOHiQXlwvxuB9QMah7sb9HBbzVaggUbnnuayDuf+4ZmsrPP1qolVqba0dTKhTnxJRB3JtJXSz8M2JbQt/T3/sY9m83UwFU1L8PQVrrlz+EGX1kCLkTYYhh2mATFwTPfAf4hzOGyqn1GfEdy8KT6ZDessRtYa6YdA5StnhbYiiPdX1whSsjdQOaTAW63UXuauETNnJ+Sl6HFVKQ9GkD+Ad/i+UiI+tHdpirl8/oBnmaKWR3NBvaiQuc0mOtJSSfoB+nyeShE80QOTst1vwG4d/ao9dk1hgriPdzmvezaT3fL1T9Nt8AaaDwScrbsrixv0cFvNVqCBRuee5rIO5/fvVwOqZcdC8LmN2ANjMvTlGMNX7/H+V3JsmhTnfxYBTTyk9GUozBmYUukosWZ+hS6jtVka5rKaEtnBLQPMFVLhMjfMB+Jxflch6KwVCXmiIlPFiwdbg/JrogR/J5B6pXrWJti+XWNH/JUdIBxo0fboAjEH9efJd0J6fBRZa8ioXmPRKVeLMFPyB1kD1SyZwkWdEydd0WsYvjTIpFK8DwdvoKUo+An2Nl+Xp5Hgsh/wx5MwGIAlPrukHVMllekXR6aTsdUwaPRFE7ka4V/2yT35mNjSVhhnp0ksE4GqXepVXYNjpvJRsXYrmnLs8kkhdv+kvxD6BFqDgu9+YvWb7VGR+Z9OlTK316LTC0UIrq3/IeC+kdjv/IKeAGChyIxYT60Bw0Fuf5p2dyg3LULaYnQxXMosSZXcUa9BI8DxJxMIoHD4IYUjJkuZu4gGnw5SkBQy9RIuTltazk/HQhHYU+Pf1DaKCVWwZqSh2g2Bvu+nE\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19010","langCode":"vi","question":"65ZEhwoKebc04mY4Y+Gw04NVHowKhuZOEywDJIVZkmzZbn1HZtRQFpdfsa1bzQ9jdw2JkE4j/5PHhyUu6XJMiw\u003d\u003d","answers":["would leave","will leave","leave","would have left"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE3oozZJRnED21oB6Jl4SVFRO/qRIMDQaohWwtACz+7Oc2xAKsLbiugrPkv+KT3CZzXaiMgbpKOCvD9ShK8sKdJq2UhP4iv31fckH6ogMwAM/1JM044fs198ctPG3fVaPYrw/htt8zjyQCKR/zpdA/J3DHf99zxUyyKFSrSfN/vtZxiho+4FjWZMBdYh7o2IgGYwknyY1OegLbFqqxh6HSy9Ryz4Wh6KdqpzQPgVQe5X33xVFA7BgkuknBLG9Ov3nOCcPuoNEUZCB1YE5lXxn804PAsQRXX9RcSsf/HqH9igJiCKxqxwigfPvh2AR2IB7I80h2zrfQ2IptbqDeGLvgkXDU70vBAneJp2D8wwm61PDgwX6gDc0BdRwVlWRiZjLktXucwE9e+pSpcYWG5gut77UkzTjh+zX3xy08bd9Vo9iDspaHFuCTFOOtDvjKO82Hal68BVkXe2XJqrOvpSDxCzVah2oO/KjQknm5+4A3w6pG8tcSwIVRzFy53CgGNpBw5dWlNPBxQ5TuLzl9PEakIF1m8gtsJwtBEJYpcPJCSMCuCJ2s4gF28IgtOO87sNV1WcMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuIOIG/P1RtDtKeJMhYwH+eylfXRsBi6iaMN+avUeJahBypnNghkvCeIHqYru5hvQkmFa3fwZazYzI+HrBtZLNr/FtmdKiyDbTGuIzvIkvKAZBAv2j7kzU0MME2Tpt5DdUAVl1nF8Fzgy1lQUgnyJbCTOPs6oUsZAIUA9ZuokV04dWsCFpRFtGDadJpfQNYFRq2epoXyExGPvCQqzDwjMTBvf6eoTixwPIQ9uvxPsTjZq6ka9lGbezQo+qh7hqwoxvs\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19011","langCode":"vi","question":"/MEvv44k/9tnBv+Cjkpky2e2jCqAyeC4SVe7Ft3uC/9ph4AqxFFoVT0Htj5XRqegEma9S0olWum0/Nf0z6CdY6pvpcGXMhqUX5MVgZZhru9kwiihhZ0XGs4yh7Hz8URh","answers":["ask","would ask","asked","will ask"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+Wtyd4AGRlwKdbOZrHOBqInGpOJ6OH05WMKENRkrUmo7oiH2qCeUuxIpd+jn5iTSQhIEHo7RrwGdTM2+4BMzXwrfiJOHiQXlwvxuB9QMah7sb9HBbzVaggUbnnuayDuf+4ZmsrPP1qolVqba0dTKhTnxJRB3JtJXSz8M2JbQt/T3/sY9m83UwFU1L8PQVrrlz+EGX1kCLkTYYhh2mATFwTPfAf4hzOGyqn1GfEdy8KT6ZDessRtYa6YdA5StnhbYiiPdX1whSsjdQOaTAW63UXuauETNnJ+Sl6HFVKQ9GkD+Ad/i+UiI+tHdpirl8/oBnmaKWR3NBvaiQuc0mOtJSSfoB+nyeShE80QOTst1vwG4d/ao9dk1hgriPdzmvezaT3fL1T9Nt8AaaDwScrbsrixv0cFvNVqCBRuee5rIO5/fvVwOqZcdC8LmN2ANjMvTlGMNX7/H+V3JsmhTnfxYBTTyk9GUozBmYUukosWZ+hS6jtVka5rKaEtnBLQPMFVLhMjfMB+Jxflch6KwVCXmiJXjuYm798jlmPypkJOmZYo6vVdzcJgLegDxUuIlTwQ/llPE5FQAAc9dHYc/2HQu4mv6k/+KdpukFn1F8E6SfG2/jsCfA1dSNr8bzmW7DxzQkAj46MJ8wFWZUUF0ZoQfdgjjbN88n3U+grGmjcpZcu4IoXgB1B2djgBPWp1MFjdFLDaDemGuNuRDEJpLDal8HhYpkeWCEIBPM4SkPYZAXNavlQuBPJJXGJEp5NjIG8rOjrlHOgemKg1EnNeMPRjknBWFfPCw4/miRTP4sojWBujxIIUJJZ1wEhtoMQWyFVbzK9L/SovVr13lYl/Zy8PO5X5xL/JKQgMALjn9/KfjkrHA1aIcsEvo7xzW+AZLrAk4UO2crgP7emLzfeYSN9AuyoK0+PxBoB1Ok8l3y7E8XiNYMMpy8Sm7dGfROtBu1ssG8koxsF38T8Mck1+XqhMiBw\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19012","langCode":"vi","question":"JP1BpJU8Z41IZok21vPLm7hMAp2htJud5NoCJunKzV5wQXetI8ZebKW7+jtBj761","answers":["would have taken","will take","could take","takes"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE3DG7/hPG0oNXZxCV8PhFIkREPVDhoP5q5SWBNTy5BZ+9sGXgvlfv3EI+DP+JzM1o0tWJMCICCREg2gw9W0f4zQg265EjrjWU3GOTKgyRCi+3ypvB5SzlFrc370fteFUi5qXT9tctyg9r3MXbpdXG99qgG1y8tVGN6YlzJgHZYRHW23u0Hqj5csX+t05H7ntGbPS6Qx41blIB5WwbWwdwQc9HedqeH6sAJve/wY5zc30wxzXv6c390LOvQ7JEUSlylFgtMUbDLf/oK6S19qidK1JsklN4ioC985DzlTRN6vnF6iDXZOHYr4n17DEim4JhCr6mBE5jGPBiuSm2Ikg12rQcSHHBtWAu12DnDVGnvj5t5GSwWmQ/lZKAzSjsOb3X1A7SZmb4gTCvfMnUGC877vfKm8HlLOUWtzfvR+14VSLDi/NtLzN5EkPxkItDBjVnOSI/pkgA0Xx1AxGexnCxVtWEHaff8pjqErF8AbGeZ/cMnf6t5m99xBDHUzt/ajssksM/IYaGxBd7DruLdYj3Hu3IMtxPDnEj2sQe6+gTYXPmyY33bHu5ltnVCqJAohlhwB1pmAMKtDJXZZlEBP6ERhPrb9sWigMkJvZd6qzWjYyP4QZfWQIuRNhiGHaYBMXBEsM/IYaGxBd7DruLdYj3HsjfVIz7+jioQZMDbf/JXVUfrJp4GnzvSDrY8gKcxY/NJYAN9A3lVFRJ7vq66gB+kDnyDmqaeKcthR1JBk1umN0uCJ2s4gF28IgtOO87sNV1WcMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuKa/x8uFTeV6rNeniWXh+V8+iDCSIYJ8e6h1i8mOUMU+/wkNpzgYMROGMXi2PVHedPXHrQuxcRtUzYpGKaMnmxwIz1yCLuAfIvR3JJ42xaQpkYBcOJzKsnER7YLuW3Izk9gom3w3L/SobDwNr+yCGW6JmTWaSrdMJdYJjQ7YLN6Jy+6Mx3NfLYAoZ5Ald3URhqgs9mCj8vHwRWJ/s/AogMmnDsa6SFzUmxm7FXZlvGf6CsTgFOT55Yiw8fJt6eLkR+tSIiF51Mywt5fsLuZm6tkNcVz3t6JczHMRtjARSuqRp/RtQUFcAYpDvsOcTyBAHVeJmxQLdPSxzYMep7MrUouf025vfoBXx8ZwVV0m7VRFSjmfGOMFW2eAilNzHc7Ivm1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19013","langCode":"vi","question":"QQZOFCtgebYHc0IXTMWoJgU2Ek6/IRGEUNj2Lh7BPJ7m4dvKxkXkGls1ibbsFBuWcbHcz3CnemplfPiP4rLDZQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["will do","would have done","might do","does"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeExPjG3cZRsNHLCvsbAPUxJX2TZanaiCRtlDpG+gISoWWbWg/O9hTSfSjLCgZSyeGDsUXjOv4beG70KLFZZeDutyvTRZ8qJSjPd4BTXbXuVjtbL3VHAra8L/CZ9YcplD0K5HXa4rVD1mF/NPWTCCG2nHTel4/ALOkqaJr0/TFG/e+JYSFWyjUnnQA0HKPiaBV1VuX1SEOMN+VUw6Fi3W+xRzewz4KNIWsaML49nblWv4jTOZVkkXjBpFebUJweXnhM5ukttM9qs9yDuKdnR2hm/A+n4kGR5Nl/S/RPXZGQMq+FsQiFDbQZQa9c54ZGpHmN++o+VosZE6MiJWg3Ft8Udq5yGtjEOaDt3hWcjGRpzT566uL3gJ+cei9X1+NJ/F2QFKX3DwKsUuu/f/B7SeXFytsvdUcCtrwv8Jn1hymUPQrU8w/L79Y+TPHbW1sBLQ6E5XDsy3G8io3iCKY+PgO0BhXMFM1rELVI0lw7sutYJXd4HIqkWoC52vsfTFRrk7FTVxUdfbxK0y5HJ65wGOr0sTzIe/JUji2WhTmPtUXwsTQgBvHuuRti7mNol+IsdTWIOC+PsSjoHrMzYhRX5uU0HBSvk/ijfY4Rrbo2R/9d0dHwFJVeO4Tq47q1ut5mDXEnxMjfMB+Jxflch6KwVCXmiLVslPH2UBvkb38zq0SvUL8Gcucg51sv1BNPdNxnth2WcBhbKa9hMlMy6qPjwQp8ryF7ZonnYLM+VBkm42m/ZePEKhUjgxYaCX43AVH3+29ARll+ijAJe+juitIA+vUc420WiHxkpSkC15h+v4TM29Can4fU/erFKIGcY1bk8XT3nyWvplZ4PtfNOhI/3q2SmKPtz620p9iHNSikyrF+cJ881V7ssNZlxAuHDJC2ozc+uu+snBQgN8bPOKqm1S2jHH1YyKfWWxzopaLFyY0EmgmBBZudeq/Hu3TaV1fK6ORlOFo7YFwVgWQEHF2Ju2ZStr+JCsI295Yn/iYyBgCzIe0oXpduIunJQr+HAS9CvzsehZPq0mbDTcGzDHPskms5+jbeUb+Zqh33Qm23cSPxgGR9x4Gm30ZRELWGC0Sog1uEg69BA+IgZRtffR6baP8tWo5j1FSSLAm8o78hYf5S9fCjAxnvK7J9TfScz+MP6qrgzI/WkKS3bE4O/7ibC28tZeEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19014","langCode":"vi","question":"bBlBwBqaCAW8LilTIoRAhPSzk2qlrIGZhjNtkB0yd4gAHWyJfrQtOFnl7FC5cyTd","answers":["is","be","would have been","were"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8G1+oTMiX1dSJkDQnjfpPWA15+xvBQvzog2OIFYnJuAxDS6p5N4bnVUoXJw65gam/c6wOfLSjSo9DJ4Q/OIxMw3deLCnL/9fHmgs+ZXZ+BjG8qgf+xqSFLJktwhoAdP/kGpkzjTf6a75cNuAYnVmNCnBwAjmqJl782UM4UvAB6z/pVp/fba72zkI22DHVLUFdmz1L6t2OTYeIEGt80J0QbzMQ2ejwLGYiEUrCVdINwoVPmmvn6svHGQ2U1oDKivq4mR2vms8lGocyVtVY251/hb2rmGkThvlEW/MT5esxvwEpWX15BVlIxgAK5Lg3ojQTsxEA9faxI2qxQhNC1zPAEaGGcRJD55hPowQOPRO0nwUt0YeRuIZA4h0aTIchnYRegip6wHKyqJWgxiOM8ReLWaodF5z2gK+WoaRkl7LUPalzAheqQkAkxV4C+OHyDm9SsyPpn/tPt40BFL+rlTDYMtTV0KPG84e5qI7C3q0msHZwc2Qd35dWPCFj76PYlzfAEb/AX5DYWX7qEbH+eyds+5Mpu6dIOTu/sHb7eC9CMp0jIKf8vym1WtpR2+jJYFzxg3DmxPqMhIf59vtJRfmWZhzv4sN6eW64okS3ZF8UQiQndyzYnnVvXIeATlXZSUfXMIQKHlql0GalN3UgcVqOuA8fOYyu/TG6gA4KQFbFVtlz2CMEzm8cnWAl3rC4VgwiSypEay3n3d86rs3hjayuUSyhsolBluGl++nIeWdbZSs4EuwPNCgIh+rgmhAgbmRluX1SEOMN+VUw6Fi3W+xRwIeBNMHPfYHb2FLbh/sV3B12fgAi8lR2tn0j4rJSFEVEUnxSwTUO8M0TmXTLp6OGTug9VfQbDSlReG62l2lM59DlG3ZKIKfy1x8P6D71Bdz8RcU2sOBS6xlHDShdoD8sg1SJGUziPzKmQoq8dH4vmWiGKpQ6r5UU8sKXG5FJ2IGM2fAQipu32RZEw0UkjF18NWnz/2LhaI3Sc+Y0ySOuapCSDJoN07LgqDN2TAxVSjZ1tt7tB6o+XLF/rdOR+57RlMuzmVAB2uouxUCvzjKuM4h7w2ebxe5lNMvYCkS0xs2rBCrJt4BUub1da7fAIpG5wHRQQra+iMzPs/wcqUHRe45xkP3nspDs4pGM+qY4UtNw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19015","langCode":"vi","question":"LfTIi8tFXk8x8fKdrX0d1q0iVklxFAHv+Q40JCgjY6EqtCeFxelcJMTk3U2AN4Xk","answers":["am","is","are","were"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8G1+oTMiX1dSJkDQnjfpPWA15+xvBQvzog2OIFYnJuAxDS6p5N4bnVUoXJw65gam/c6wOfLSjSo9DJ4Q/OIxMxf+PQyD88mSs+lsf2q4iHqRawwoFYr0RsNUocvykp23KKXIWFjWRqxNhGseXuxybIfpDWeyP8p4cKPcnSlX1XK0YdZi7TaLvpB8yBHqd0rGPgxa2KvbgnnX9DRV31uQS0nJ1NGnEbw8qKbDs37rWaxRLMIKNMjAA/pPhBaJEtGpRsJloOoZsE+mhb+SSbpiguVU9EYQcgIpKxZovcXZcgQ63G5hAOWH7W8wqrONODmuJV79YeZe6z8eKWP97Vjcob2NxxcW8LsC4nMBm8I6g1LVQw6Nf1xQ8Gz0Ax+tdyAXRoowFXqP2R1SbEApnxV9eT3VPvg8zMqIa/R40VEEFNrEyN8wH4nF+VyHorBUJeaItdXmmBf/BVZYLVT5EmwpI7BAU9P/aX9F0up/s4r8mVhnOcIO7KNYGfPc6fbMHwkd+j8X6GRT4C0l3R69eSju51yu5UJvFBYrBuoWnYDvtDiL5OhtMfcv2puDlWyKkIququWpXf39mVGky7gunY7QFVK54wRsAWQh39cTM5X+D0wYx2wSfz3dO7vuhnCt2ugG9phijovavCEIWJ5u/CMGwVtKINg+506g7Db2SUVD1GwvaAWS3vdTSAWxLKIM6suYdFbyoHyIbj5PDwQ1z+pTIuIaCNNXX3R9pO2hIGci1cw4XhvFZCbL9tpk09oXyJCtu65HcdVHQezowua8IDXUg7dRt8WMS6t5lKtC33Op0zZEKhUjgxYaCX43AVH3+29ARll+ijAJe+juitIA+vUc41YXF0kwdOBzUxdg83y8wg7qSt7X35UWP6jZq+1lprinNkepdW3Jo56fHkyqmTtRDFXnVb6oSg4T7CsAMMmjA5dJxssJSK8i19X3wAHFR6Po0/WD9oGiku15oMCgkeDEvuBKZ39WWxuA9zMwlBXQR8/rxd/m8U2RWaBonCqPoll1pklAEVs/mSxoBoLxTYnJIpObUNmtKcQyNmjz/SiyZk8x/SdOTVdN1g60YDeFdpiUQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19016","langCode":"vi","question":"+mXAEvAyrDc4MF5hSbLOrV9k2w4KUAGDLKURpn6IurQeq9iCqK2go6KwU4E+3cNaA4WydYF/Gjn4IBELBpl8NA\u003d\u003d","answers":["were to visit","visit","were visit","visits"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE98uXoZCIIzfMZ9GSa2f5nqhCsIRpSM3U9syHTT/ygcMpNmZlxIRF5ZJuFNzeqJe1qwBP77qLT2JYwmCNKS3O0EniDwioGeXBBCn6oleaUkvaoBtcvLVRjemJcyYB2WER1tt7tB6o+XLF/rdOR+57Rmz0ukMeNW5SAeVsG1sHcEHPR3nanh+rACb3v8GOc3N9MMc17+nN/dCzr0OyRFEpcpRYLTFGwy3/6CuktfaonStSbJJTeIqAvfOQ85U0Ter5xeog12Th2K+J9ewxIpuCYQq+pgROYxjwYrkptiJINdq0HEhxwbVgLtdg5w1Rp74+beRksFpkP5WSgM0o7Dm919QO0mZm+IEwr3zJ1BgvO+73ypvB5SzlFrc370fteFUiw4vzbS8zeRJD8ZCLQwY1ZzkiP6ZIANF8dQMRnsZwsVbVhB2n3/KY6hKxfAGxnmf3DJ3+reZvfcQQx1M7f2o7LJLDPyGGhsQXew67i3WI9x7tyDLcTw5xI9rEHuvoE2Fz5smN92x7uZbZ1QqiQKIZYeePT8f0rFd1Zpd8xIXci+j8qtDm5ynbHoQ6XBLgDq+AfAPvrYDhZrtlynPmwz7D08f0aMq/DmH3yX1BlA25ekp46wuzwwXi9tiRYEgl2r80LC/0KbqgzoQWRT83CgbHGwqUNSyHPHmtEjjSZwNnzXPyfJt/zOOmF475DcnB8Ak0rTRSKy0tbNraw36Vy7Kd7wdUMUnx4ic7uLiTYXY1knKgmZOiKKOfvQrmcl7xVYDgXRB97WCTOvvGdHYkgFMahgIyWd7ybFUcd2+5CM0g3qgoIK/xbhqsxtwBtFFBGGM8nSq2e/FVCvasb0CJ9aGgui5cvxLhck+ozu3+JDzF02W0GkdJFK/uV6TTucSsnbCdrDMi6ytHAXta3RclrcKM3KFi7SQgnYYdkxVyP9b3cMSPzxWui2B0mlemB9BYJaqerSDvwLcb4DlJN52oPPKeK7PbXQXoqyiSJj520zLomrLiOcHN/xJdLfYtuynIcNvGFBxVPhFEaacHYhA5Ht2x8ZSqJi2hAdrS5CvfGs7jO7TfmIdrOIJV1v2LJWYVrkudD4IbEeD/Zw+VrC1pJop/2BPQIfKnnB3noHtOg61xLDgY/ql61cSLeT33zvsuYZ58HUHFeSJAs8WtmNvcDBqfYDi5Xe3m8WIuVxJ3sHomVDhJHZbCXbBQ9YRWiaGErVU1zcPtfCj/zjKG+HrYuCeXEDss0/WMaXOetynuwCxkrUYnjd54u+BmZPwVVFqcKhLBzA53EWVKY6XIk4oTZgC93wMrzYIuerYgf635jPUz/u3awIWlEW0YNp0ml9A1gVGrZ6mhfITEY+8JCrMPCMxMG9/p6hOLHA8hD26/E+xONmrqRr2UZt7NCj6qHuGrCjG+w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19017","langCode":"vi","question":"lLLTIdc+XSC/IOJjY8WZJwLyj0AB0XOeal6Rcsv6Ivhb4FWE/dtQrA8WcnVWufhJLot9RGptcD1/uh6Xlu8SSA\u003d\u003d","answers":["will look","would have looked","look","would look"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE3oozZJRnED21oB6Jl4SVFTSmezLB9oSEORqjI8y/WUp2xAKsLbiugrPkv+KT3CZzXaiMgbpKOCvD9ShK8sKdJq2UhP4iv31fckH6ogMwAM/1JM044fs198ctPG3fVaPYrw/htt8zjyQCKR/zpdA/J3DHf99zxUyyKFSrSfN/vtZxiho+4FjWZMBdYh7o2IgGYwknyY1OegLbFqqxh6HSy9Ryz4Wh6KdqpzQPgVQe5X33xVFA7BgkuknBLG9Ov3nOCcPuoNEUZCB1YE5lXxn804PAsQRXX9RcSsf/HqH9igJiCKxqxwigfPvh2AR2IB7I80h2zrfQ2IptbqDeGLvgkXDU70vBAneJp2D8wwm61PDgwX6gDc0BdRwVlWRiZjLktXucwE9e+pSpcYWG5gut77UkzTjh+zX3xy08bd9Vo9iDspaHFuCTFOOtDvjKO82Hal68BVkXe2XJqrOvpSDxCxcLFsIA+XZ74d2UHOJqfbPINJck4CbhbNyy1DnDje5NW2g87af8JeTo2bcMjah54EBG/wF+Q2Fl+6hGx/nsnbPMkvmSqnl+SHU1NGeByCgQ+OcA6+Gj5WmcAxLPr8hdPx0+VlKPu/1O0zPOZUb/fWHofPp3vLFPlGKV5Me1Vq9IWT6pcoeRE8gNW5cmMzRV7SodqrECYqFwt5Z3WF9u1swID9UDKetBkWM2ke3+15VD5COb+uuvRR0qAN5xh8KF+ujypzCqwwokz3+gGzzEXTIf7hjjBFJAaYwdbhZF6NEc4e8Nnm8XuZTTL2ApEtMbNqwQqybeAVLm9XWu3wCKRucB0UEK2vojMz7P8HKlB0XuOcZD957KQ7OKRjPqmOFLTc\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19018","langCode":"vi","question":"oiqoXLu1PUp/78oR7xaog/gDTTbePEjOCmQwcysD4MdFNFhQnIiENuka6kV7sp9TVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["will take","take","took","would have taken"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE1mJTcCbCT40q/UAmGSOUeRB8hhTQQ6Drhgl5MRu+wALlAmwfgu0gjqBmOwGMmK5/0GHEXOxsDj2n8Ho4mirLrGXMCF6pCQCTFXgL44fIOb1hOFdKlkhwXWa18DW3FsRSOvQmkK0n1RJjApWu1vksf/kIK1nPSzM/NhUj5gq0e4D23lG/maod90Jtt3Ej8YBkQV//MliMqpp7Y2Io8mBTWuv8+WnZIKXwKqo54tewr0IOFoNRTQxbJia0UmcqQafb0326hYhwbNp2mfMj1wlCbAMfgHE9a3kuTF4tHi4HzGG9iAzEgPiUmrdntkoCYpQ8X/5e4vcRaZTjXYQu2Lafw/Bb85DXeTkzRirOpHFAcoE1FzJWarBYvCZ4e/LpYrTvql68BVkXe2XJqrOvpSDxCzZPJOQsokqNeOuwH5EVdO3z5zH40CqKT1WqgW29uWPR8/FAEk0YlTNnEpe0vYAL6QwfU/veUaNbpxx0HJWRsnefggyTtvNx6KjRJ5G3AwWxF25Qqwuoh+QHtRSqvqPixKj3j+bePF33M+bdZ6couqTbG6MWXsI5al/0Uk8C1bM9dg2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF29I1ZaucamLp3cm00Kk4RtLbB8NsWe9BhbPEe6DvkDLs+4eMMp2IEcnVNzf3sJ6niuxmn6qgGz89XqjVTgp7f6/OUqoRoLP6IjlSeObp4tpdRJht1MjiLLt/2393hCu0lgijV4ho3OywxDNm03rqzirRt9lHtWvwW1xLZRUuaDf8CLH3ZaM56NArOwL4FSVcmTDnxoNeRQXBm8l8YSnyNEif025vfoBXx8ZwVV0m7VRFcNq4bWp3pU/znaPpAKq60A\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19019","langCode":"vi","question":"ojRBzO9CMZtVx8ZrYYx2SG4pfDfjRFPImdsA0U6Kg2XnbKMBoAACX0sYwQZu6W9K","answers":["would have met","met","meet","will meet"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE1mJTcCbCT40q/UAmGSOUeRVijiGYTVfDCZWbEEODej5Nz9qiBJAw7RL7bzLKLFqaCbVO+8OFyJmSC7lC7ALS4iqV/U5MBcjr3JFRKdS07p4KajO0tvGl77OyT+gNdLQwpFSFdV81YJ+TlU6s1p7G4Il659pNBpa/+F9CxUv7sxcrUiIhedTMsLeX7C7mZurZPU/IERNsYfeDi2fAUnuyrwbPZ1ztVhHTsWrPiUQ7LX3ROB9tCQUzsGVKWTmqRNLnQUII5UBBe2beV0dGRJil3k0ZXPwzlmgrAnG84aE2QIHNsw169EjURoxOQd+hwxmHKDRaZ8pt57ojlfAeDYfNbergNOa801xE1uPAV0nP0w8zRRU3JWLNBxjChliREDiIWJL7dmBrd+c6BnLh+oszFUbWHFE8QsuJ+mJ7qjMzDTPPix+bFvympASrzMxcFNx48f5W0B+hYw/SmW1fi2jaUc7Kd3BYQicVPuCRE3K5KyHwK5POBiPM1L21JmyVraNWFBpXDaBzEni4UtsUklX5jGxuACVM/k1MGYi/QUvasudXqnP6AYHYv/N72S567fIUE9Ah8qecHeege06DrXEsOBj+qXrVxIt5PffO+y5hnnwvarUhA1K1UdS3eEfGR5aNPLZCdCF1EIlzcYVPtVEwo1Ms+F7VLv4cCarYMG2ZqJH1m91M7hEiJR8LB1NhNuDV2Gr6DU2MLTmr9oXkn7TUc5LaBdmhfLXiEaznpC0ft9wMi13axANO+i2qHN5uRCXXmf7gie9edC2f/x5hr/UF4ELaRdhVUK/x8xc9N40ZoBD"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19020","langCode":"vi","question":"JyTtdu8I2PoE/2mG2Mui8PJbI2dBMY56AkEwUdZVfQp7aOeEENpm4OW+cFNaigB2","answers":["have contacted","contact","could have contacted","will contact"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE2t/Dr+owUumUzSP94B6mvrjXt/Q53r5pgYDWn3B79Y+TWWnmz3wFRSPx2io2tUW5yS1JOSBCm0st/P4a5l+iaRTK45jBPp3u/U/jgZmyR6iHpQpIyg8bRM6tCjnN+KVxQ94R0yfkH3FDli1nmYM3Kebzcu5umrs6obnRherB6Pzwx3/fc8VMsihUq0nzf77WcYoaPuBY1mTAXWIe6NiIBnOwez+n5uSorsFlOBfB+XJ6fHWytlMRPjLqd1XNGNiTDopk2fzmGqw91mtH2/9UsTbVkdNmk9qPdOlyT+/x4RjjYSJnKfObSH91qQW7xKS4rmMpTh0y/lf6y9OKhSU/BXi0qz4J/zLrOcNlx7sw8L7Ro2wDrRoksoJqg5SvzPymKpX9TkwFyOvckVEp1LTungUmwiskiFSAbG88F3B3v/XNplpxlgtGUwuBKBYFZ3Bt/EQ21Ee6W4s20SGf/64+EFNaW2VfNBOgO4CA+4pV0TsankdNprrnCfh0vnPVkAbde2eakhMv6gjRbPhGvNyC2/rhMO/rKwvC9q7QQ+PSlzA4WRu/wEyP7QPxHPN0tEx/66OevsZ4wrV1TZ1qQr3wrolgMXI5UK6isAnPbpHjnei4pXM2fLO4hhbGuOlz2YCFBctDvrtBAiqAAhrtu7RcjrJRmx7M/P2qwGHq8FqUv9ecHzFpzjh/csA2nnmlMCsUJ7YqSzByHUAq/eFu9cQ1v+vxfLzm1tnBGg+MsGMi4rPnqVNtPF/MP3h4TFMVeZbiKQ/V08l2PoobHn9ZJTrRPuVXSIPwwRFQ/PY3mjs5l5Agmm4QwmRMpyBKWqYLjMvK/CblpvFDZsRSSpUIfuOOIKjnkYyLo9M3tA+JWWgPpX7"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19021","langCode":"vi","question":"fx1frURI2jue12/4WXk8K6/JFQlH2SRwJxwGu6Lel5+SvhqmiRRuhu597xH4AKJdkGXSpDc5KN/EHJmzAYgfqHGw/tnWInEmhbURjT6rS9VUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["might have missed","missed","will miss","miss"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEySwpeERqlq8q+6mp2lquxAtu49ND2C3cjKg84me7sGZ/wAjK03vr1I8l6T4YB3G3sQ0uqeTeG51VKFycOuYGpv3OsDny0o0qPQyeEPziMTMX/j0Mg/PJkrPpbH9quIh6sFvzkNd5OTNGKs6kcUBygS7eJ0LmgEELB6X0uFcmQ4303pePwCzpKmia9P0xRv3vvv+yGo3q+fpqd+3Ym8XdPuKklfZwan3wvpAdGgh1LKpb2bYU48CBpo4RUKQbh9zVQkWAbcVnSh92u3pOoAlZjpfkswa8eWrx2zyTAuFpWyGSmB8Czs1MYtHGoNgSEwyMb7q0oyMlVlbq2HGkmhfmN5zI3EnLdPFyNAxXUH9FhsxZQokqVcw/m+0hw5p1MxwIhIb4E6hWrJL0bq0TsdVdNmACrL01dybzlLewvf/+pykmgQu7XZb1eEZsZyn8bo8TAM2PdCDXc1/Dw6i2p91ipZGSPDq+s1z4eDwQak10Q+zoIglmjayWgX/A9k2qLEdtwH7TLk9NJgckEcQcSgpqtFPPBlJnlnl6y6z0sRBJ44oP8edOa8IrW1Fm7tFn9V6c4BspkZvueLXA73LbK1igfi9Xqvq/lNkBvh/ADlUjVqzBxEINbq2E37TR50kBOWhaCiWnLSf0Zzm8cgTQyTe6eiH+G/jYHLHNZItsdGLkSvpH9rBxpNB5ayKEoKqomV7xU3KJcn5RiflOwDAzhl88DUSgyrFne04dhNFPBzKZH9RNgD4QYWXcvOrd2rzssjeTbOXhqda4I5ucJ9JtjW/aLHk5jIfd5Lgig9hzMN6+p/7Pv2Vqbz51Z8MH/k5v2ds+nMXlMRemxcBeFM6Hns8uBXsMboU7Q9sf4zS9xDI1czzt3leKyShU0DjZOjD57irE03T3pwey6DLA519wEWrHPU\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19022","langCode":"vi","question":"K8IVui4Pl6eWDCj/Yw4Jt5y4sWdSxF4DnCynkgD74DhRzysN0pw6/RYal4U7kv0wuXMpj5VMBkdT7F0/xGtjrg\u003d\u003d","answers":["passed","would have passed","will pass","pass"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE1mJTcCbCT40q/UAmGSOUeST0cux89OCVKFBHSSnnMxc/wAjK03vr1I8l6T4YB3G3sQ0uqeTeG51VKFycOuYGpv3OsDny0o0qPQyeEPziMTMX/j0Mg/PJkrPpbH9quIh6sFvzkNd5OTNGKs6kcUBygS7eJ0LmgEELB6X0uFcmQ4303pePwCzpKmia9P0xRv3vvv+yGo3q+fpqd+3Ym8XdPvPfAf4hzOGyqn1GfEdy8KTb2bYU48CBpo4RUKQbh9zVQkWAbcVnSh92u3pOoAlZjpfkswa8eWrx2zyTAuFpWyGSmB8Czs1MYtHGoNgSEwyMb7q0oyMlVlbq2HGkmhfmN5zI3EnLdPFyNAxXUH9FhsxZQokqVcw/m+0hw5p1MxwIhIb4E6hWrJL0bq0TsdVdNmACrL01dybzlLewvf/+pykmgQu7XZb1eEZsZyn8bo8TAM2PdCDXc1/Dw6i2p91ipZGSPDq+s1z4eDwQak10Q+zoIglmjayWgX/A9k2qLEdtwH7TLk9NJgckEcQcSgpqtFPPBlJnlnl6y6z0sRBJ44oP8edOa8IrW1Fm7tFn9V6c4BspkZvueLXA73LbK1igfjbybAxKzEFP7/Dg1mmGEK64zmfX5hdGCEr+5Upkks86SiWnLSf0Zzm8cgTQyTe6eiH+G/jYHLHNZItsdGLkSvpH9rBxpNB5ayKEoKqomV7xQl+EVODTTaaFds9UET2zPK4remdo8eh9PRLTSYDlPbaosGxzd7jkALc5+7rxQx5eB5Um51tUwaQaYPZOdbzNFqN5iYrK+Euek+qNeHlwrQU"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19023","langCode":"vi","question":"FhN/YavJN2XjOwwxCTlbD5NFMRMHNereF/IhQDc4Jsbrfc68ktWCpq8x3VRUfBbWVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["is","will be","is being","would have been"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE1mJTcCbCT40q/UAmGSOUeTtBVMLvgxY2eAtJy6HNrDN2V1G5OCeOs/uL8Aj9NF0ETHJLviFm64BLdpz/Qnamsyq9qhfsGBCEl120S+nyRO/+rwWSV+DNYnDwFzcLl8d7MFvzkNd5OTNGKs6kcUBygS7eJ0LmgEELB6X0uFcmQ4303pePwCzpKmia9P0xRv3vvv+yGo3q+fpqd+3Ym8XdPvPfAf4hzOGyqn1GfEdy8KTb2bYU48CBpo4RUKQbh9zVQkWAbcVnSh92u3pOoAlZjpfkswa8eWrx2zyTAuFpWyGSmB8Czs1MYtHGoNgSEwyMb7q0oyMlVlbq2HGkmhfmN5zI3EnLdPFyNAxXUH9FhsxZQokqVcw/m+0hw5p1MxwIhIb4E6hWrJL0bq0TsdVdNmACrL01dybzlLewvf/+pykmgQu7XZb1eEZsZyn8bo8TAM2PdCDXc1/Dw6i2p91ipZGSPDq+s1z4eDwQak10Q+zoIglmjayWgX/A9k2qLEdtwH7TLk9NJgckEcQcSgpqtFPPBlJnlnl6y6z0sRBJ44oP8edOa8IrW1Fm7tFn9V6c4BspkZvueLXA73LbK1igfjUkr187K2EBVqWKJGFjBlO/7GlFboIbnIqAXzKmUgNFxNaI290ePLCrqrbskiquqC4InaziAXbwiC047zuw1XVZwy+C9/jcLrCMX49Na3O4lh4qQcfVEJNFXlVq7Jur4M8qnuB3+NQVpSbMKAbv2hvPGA+vVAAc86xqyNSw9FkhPdbOzskeAg+J2tRGw4wbPdZM/iyIlvTcZ6xIlnNb9DQrLLo+O4Pg2hKefNgaFV09A\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19024","langCode":"vi","question":"MlT1v9OV8SvWY9Ox4UBxgAFqRCBOWRC24rtOzdVqQEsaQ3qggS/cexwNdMovX4cXELVQuBxn+NamUO7rGHY2T8ky5qraphZ1YPl1L9jVJSM\u003d","answers":["know","should know","will know","wouldn’t have known"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6RmzlQQ6OmsvwGogvRQWgNNuZZ2ah7Ub0S1lsLpaMva0PDWK8PsscraXBt5steqM21oPzvYU0n0oywoGUsnhg7FF4zr+G3hu9CixWWXg7rcr00WfKiUoz3eAU1217lY7YlJ+aPEcqPqr2KPT+Q4crUSDvyR2U0fWDnV76WHLUtWcIAelp5Bc8nLQXEDB1n1BkbfZR7Vr8FtcS2UVLmg3/BWyGLHRPCIeNW02EjHgjxXL0SolEv5pkD2oG2fO+opk2zuh7MexkGosVy//bRgQkRRd4UEU5FgNz0OLyGxr8xn7Q1HX/bAzUJUYliQL6cSxB+qkr7sY+7kfKGdT9iHujevV1qpKwcxTbg3b1dMi8hJy5K/Zt+sze3awE2YNAJ8vtPmHNjm6T0Bpiyn59VJL9BveE/AQXcnOXPLqL0O+MlfXxvEM600F/tDdYuM84ujRKRzvE7NwJfKu4KHT19fyj8r75iHmT/oDRetNfLD41HLOW4pR50v6rjbFZf2kUOWJM939OqVdT0w67+9SdKqgEV5MwGIAlPrukHVMllekXR6dOS0XgqsbJdLhAlcLDyBrsodDL91k3KOKKlRowP5WvK09I6ZBOiBM5bT0fZlA1xhFucbjCL7l3U89cGHnM86cdK69skBAfb07Q0Vx4ValVD5dzy6iYcxt3+SBIhLyJqLpz0dmRx06Cgc1jQDGAEjVtKtR6+LkAfht4G4pdWIvz5gcngkCEJ8lHXPefyqoXYfi0lzP/mUIdks3rYQiSkYNqxSH5M7kIc5wSBuGJJ9IzAao6vYiLZhrafIKT0ywMsZHl1PwIdhkYf0VmbH/rUSVz/qXaI/qsG/WC3u2eVDNsg\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19025","langCode":"vi","question":"vWMMR3uytgKhgAlslqKAsQIA8Z1uv3OFKNf0l9Vk5+7U5OqQkr3r0rLjCK5iAaxp","answers":["would have fined","fine","could fine","would fine"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwwNFfigrrkH099vVzRCJxjBsBqjXXTrPwJb1fkZuBTsJKdMe1F84zviA5PBN8jgtCu+pUXG2rJ8ios63yNk+cz2Z3JlSgmXFW6yxFD72s/6rfw4l5vJgrrpTFDt/5dPzVItEcage63b/xalThATh3hjEcf03bkWEhb/pwOx6LSrQamTONN/prvlw24BidWY0H+SNAOsf60j5M3CI7Ln3KtW+IR/fSKcob0FY7K1bLjaQTbPlflimlbdpTovBitTSyNiKwuRWxALSwusSUdJCf+o0RSsCCY8QvZsIbXhlZwXA44afHoO1//Pp6cWjyJfGj8Nki9dMPNg0nUeNnRFD2UsvZWW2mxYIIu7sfZ8hAp123lG/maod90Jtt3Ej8YBkWE1UyXqC5UgjEr9kuVgbJGy4/nMz7qpGQW43tXTXEJE8qtDm5ynbHoQ6XBLgDq+Aa2pczW073EZY9CtnZj4XuWUtRvqDdujogBOaj3BjWUEu2KFF8Ckml0N5jN7a9S4FRzS1kzZ6oDD+HNBFlj1/eFJO4Fp79HQvWQ9u6UL22WcWO7wHmkadqYiQHOS/9eO1mYGEYLh5JytVrhQMfCaOm0vRLwj2JZwFk6j97tn3rrln3PJoUbefBgbqGxzcOnNdO4IrB8cQf8DwAXiArRdUQwc0tZM2eqAw/hzQRZY9f3hSTuBae/R0L1kPbulC9tlnFju8B5pGnamIkBzkv/XjtZHfcXM3iNRDxCKbRKX6KSDr4ky1TP0dZQL1mjSlGl+n7QNqpMTcnLAdSF65XuqQgWqMpQGkGI8BsfxsiD/5J86bsKlI+biCgYnxMYBmXucs6LGONiG+Z5kngpslO7x1BnbVWdllZxCObxu3f+hHQBs1wXJ71YqqMPvFCnTv8O56YVzuY/BlZ0/JnxRmjkEOz90Cu3oPYv54aCrtNrywYSiNeUdoSJwWaYjco1VHp9BIO9leWlz6432A4zMO8aRjJE\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19026","langCode":"vi","question":"B8PhyHRLwW9a00E43jJfxy5C2I9qKCWjvWEbPRzkgI/ZCNdlB1GGjTmWVv2wJt94PyYBBgtLmmt0/liG7j7lbg\u003d\u003d","answers":["could have eaten","eat","would have eaten","would eat"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEw0voz/WdiVgwK+AkROS8Cu+uz9W3jTD0CCFy58S9l6Pg2XqG92FRNbGqUW4VUnHx7jjDzL+DZ9tq9Mn40E4udkSvikvdApI0FVETyQRwZDk6KxYFQYkrlI3AfLLHCVKbcJPfovwYQmjs69YySFD7ioSeu3fYvpUY/Lci6oloG5LiNjCJng/olYbXYzrw7aqk6Jj3ELzb66sOQAlw+P20i/fODi7QwiWYyx8fL51qzMn9Y4d/zNQXOJJHt+ZzqrsvJ7EU0mCXQIpa77bIqwwlqxFkrsE8DCO/LyFYUm5pEl8pRoEiIQ4vRGsUWP0Trn/XGwKB6zNuz3HGZ8iQQZoF0yagUcbKBT91YXDNZv1Ege/+cS/ySkIDAC45/fyn45Kxyu8UpC+kkfBuQZKqOVIPrlVDDo1/XFDwbPQDH613IBdm/AvIyx2IvnTUHZFP4yqBBk0jGxxFoXyCEQ5cXl7TIX+YVZ1q0CGvZXUVHdnhSNt3eJtw459Ot8euzBjTmrz6g/9d6zaRuj+OMdZOxvuaj3ysFBjMwhPvknnvshTXjb2kVRMUQBZCwk7QF0S4feIJKbmOi4O8rUlrFoVyM7gsDKhwPeLlMH0c0HaCcp/WOwgbnF5rODRME5SaJhxLNj63nfEZyBg0d52yv/LHzFJ2kUP/Xes2kbo/jjHWTsb7mo98rBQYzMIT75J577IU1429pFUTFEAWQsJO0BdEuH3iCRJIlO6t1Z8x58K8IkzyY/pQ1lD2IB+VSarRvJ8DDEO/8/CvVkSvCWt0k0v3rDsm6XhdW/f+Q2sfSffWZM+76wC8pUqVgzsEVQ3OfXFBiXrpxjemIPnOJff4D7fxBQ1Cyce6eMSf79CuKavFKe4qdwwoKuCmAt+TAtYvy0eZ/5QCPMIaxkGO76nBopZJdJhjNTBc5MBb1K8iN4Vy+avurnVbnNy+G7W6XCOHFjDCVKCV/OejblJz8w17qPPg4kKe34\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19027","langCode":"vi","question":"XTxeTJDHe2fVlsopc3RjoH0gwEBe1GjKkBP6/6Nnd598yhu6T90ZJcDSntoATr8aA1tOesVWG4whUfJTUzWY530pGuZlA+jrBbCOez4JSPBlICir6M1AugVtaKbSba6mHu/WZ4gnmZVEmOlsTbfCZg\u003d\u003d","answers":["would have let","let","would let","should have let"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7WLitbupWm9xCh4yu2t58poaVGWeNH2uJlTrfGdKajiBIm0YtMbMNN1ubuCmQUxgFK/L43OUOn/gbO6n0Df/m2G4fOzNtcO7yDWx+yYnqGQl7QDN0wMjNw/Xioo/4XJH+M8+pubOTGwVeSoosEZgd4vk4q4cMbRpAMu98Qa6TLylHxMDEGR8l3V/n1mfO+hgtXbD9bx/02FuTmj4jSPCWv/Pu/XeMogF67FiMXWz5g/4EPDJgf1IkkT8uTRif4oo4FqNKUSHpfuORD99kwyVyIrZ/WjMooVHa/I2l6No+8Z6hLoBNHQ8OoXRoU746CYzlYD8XkhFNOSkTvFDZCDfZTLgBweQyYN14rLLEycNihgWHxC8AQqwc0t+26nuM4lixQuG40is3rBp6Qy3I09rV9tAKAtiL0tasK59OhNcS6MMJE74ixuSs19zbf37Hqdt61IiIXnUzLC3l+wu5mbq2RoIzYEcDk8ailqW3LjPvI2H93EXsGIulna4JkszFP0DSpzfp9h3Cy/lBMut3yE1IMolRVgrxT75jWBmxpy+kg8ui9nC08GQtqhKF+dLijYlFYlgEFZY7FSYxCStPZcP0CUezE5T2u42o+gucp7uMY71NOpq/6EiKaHb0TLVkofBrtxhEEu67xl1u0wV9v4fz2I6JiyiHQvEnV3UJ+MyPOOdutCRymRamGiB18bADUWn1OwDgtDsCTEWlG+w7iSWN0L3JDCP9CYt4TbTPWPANPplHsxOU9ruNqPoLnKe7jGO9TTqav+hIimh29Ey1ZKHwa7cYRBLuu8ZdbtMFfb+H892szZqVdOjOkkPsgfhQd9DO7tAaNun2R9u0V0nbNkscsd2A178eoKOxn+1W5bMIazuYRQCZaWzATJVd/V+zZTcYyFEC/dRggrDDNYVzohMRxh8UoZlIDyeTPRGHBJCNeEZIgRKEVupvxhbQPhnpfy0OjbWXj5KKZtovIG0ZGt1v7p+S19ZEnOhkPhLoexlzC1hqeOo48hvyPRr/iXVHPltDXlHaEicFmmI3KNVR6fQSDD+MJ4tIv9LXbmORi4RcT1hG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19028","langCode":"vi","question":"saooUzPSXuzzRjmNDzW4V5pnBEZiGH3d0EbezqdCprt8cCKCw6XliSAIOY5ddHQ+NQ0D7WGPeagcVAnToeV8IQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["would grow","should grow","is growing","are growing"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7WrPHZisYDorOH1n4Now7f08pDmwrdy7rpJ9XJgj146OrFO7ssj4leprpSr62rBuXWEUsaloI4zC7RfOwuEk/EaZb1pX84UPrwYRUTs6iZlhmzS7GmARHsPeP9329W7OBgVB9XVxOvicSK4o+MLgYg29KoNwA3G/T7Idbh7epzODUaBXz0eo4aHfST9JB4CVx5OSTfOlKnebgET5J35o0O9tKbZbIZd83LDgjtzxIpo101GDcZkHbkSw3PE5QzYshx7+EtF10uGbWGAMsOXCHVKNrLY3WA2bH/tmJgcV3QssqOMuq6ZPDARKNchqubHdH2Q1NnvvajR83pTIAZ78Ar2025zctF6b/yNm7qbOENbn/G7TwUKuKTzv6qX4ZU4zktJV8FEfqKVkadooJtlvjkZNCc96RTaCrIjtt9lqu7U5O6ut/xHju1HUximAEbOfDMgnYi1GSm2qUliCCGzWnxjIktbK4cFbPc1fvkmblKZgqBUC02vP+5OM1oyvfWwb/cSkReqscj7snxqNGstn+7DLTqkZJSzPKmFmLRP32Uu1vAIj/0hddGM8D4BcZjC8zNyMvziwYt+eAjjt0KBn9BTOFv21Al8b8A6Ey5SNMe3NnZvd9b6FRpCWWWzpvqY5TZczNrn8CK7sN/WO5Wu96piqw+u5ZTUeJ08I30xH+mUSrB+Cr8dj+NA/NKfmxSA/9bwCI/9IXXRjPA+AXGYwvMzcjL84sGLfngI47dCgZ/QUzhb9tQJfG/AOhMuUjTHt0S82bJiPzKU1sTHCJjhkwGXWaDP4TcxvjS98NtRwu1pc/7CXKeZZ01e2kiAee/1Dr2jHJUE0RRCmuueB9uQ+A6It7Y+pDLZ+Ma6Wq1mqDCe53CikiQMvblpc+IIV7iztC/40+OuLZDmCKyclEUQt/9BpODygG7Pxfv3I2nQrP2HljWH0n9BWTVa6r/iKolh/RB61fikf21c4ymP/JuubfroNDjm7WfYWgnn922tdGdNhx6eOP+2/lz+C+Kv6+QZRGwZuPQD6cAgiEi8dNLaCqA\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19029","langCode":"vi","question":"gsU0vc0UYonnO22dUneDI58FH24ux7B2O5AzokNMYUQcVlFolorNcVb51LyfBHuq/MJFjQ5FwTaCZqwQ8eJM2YRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["go","would have gone","could have gone","went"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEyJqbPBC8f2GpimJtTsikZNeqc/oBgdi/83vZLnrt8hQg2XqG92FRNbGqUW4VUnHx7jjDzL+DZ9tq9Mn40E4udnU6gWLUXGFeXMO40z6IHXG+fdsfz+kS5LXWPPshj3mAaAdw/kGtzJXCNZf3wL7YDZmki1xJXkFa52V/ILG7lr4VzWN2LUwKuiAuep5Zfl8QYjYwiZ4P6JWG12M68O2qpOiY9xC82+urDkAJcPj9tIv3zg4u0MIlmMsfHy+daszJ/WOHf8zUFziSR7fmc6q7LyexFNJgl0CKWu+2yKsMJasRZK7BPAwjvy8hWFJuaRJfKUaBIiEOL0RrFFj9E65/1xsCgeszbs9xxmfIkEGaBdMmoFHGygU/dWFwzWb9RIHv/nEv8kpCAwAuOf38p+OSscrvFKQvpJHwbkGSqjlSD65VQw6Nf1xQ8Gz0Ax+tdyAXZvwLyMsdiL501B2RT+MqgQZNIxscRaF8ghEOXF5e0yF/mFWdatAhr2V1FR3Z4Ujbd3ibcOOfTrfHrswY05q8+oP/Xes2kbo/jjHWTsb7mo98rBQYzMIT75J577IU1429pFUTFEAWQsJO0BdEuH3iCSm5jouDvK1JaxaFcjO4LAyocD3i5TB9HNB2gnKf1jsIG5xeazg0TBOUmiYcSzY+t53xGcgYNHedsr/yx8xSdpFD/13rNpG6P44x1k7G+5qPfKwUGMzCE++See+yFNeNvaRVExRAFkLCTtAXRLh94gkSSJTurdWfMefCvCJM8mP6UNZQ9iAflUmq0byfAwxDv/Pwr1ZErwlrdJNL96w7Jul4XVv3/kNrH0n31mTPu+sAvKVKlYM7BFUNzn1xQYl66cY3piD5ziX3+A+38QUNQsnHunjEn+/QrimrxSnuKncMKCrgpgLfkwLWL8tHmf+UAjzCGsZBju+pwaKWSXSYYzUAaYo+GsLdgeFjToTmCVJ0QnaCPdrDXhAq7c+1Xd1kB7E51F8oFkCTngLXXQICSp8"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19030","langCode":"vi","question":"DXedg4sHb1RI+Sg6dwvm0cA2MDpFrDiwryMoimYc4gMHrLn2U7Y0P6q9Nuu/NLM4fIQunqMw7V1ijpPqIQ1D+A\u003d\u003d","answers":["will be","could have been","be","would not be"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+B+CqIUSZam7wLLlmus6mj2Xr2SlnJpXrc8Qa+36RqUtUrjMZuG4VUU98xA1nNYcgtDGOSyLgmtV2HTix8roQt+ri+noUgNzBCO5zm2vV0wV9sQ4KcEW6rMzOlx+U7uzFQI3uNMc7P4DQH53yVknWT2GtQ9t3YOq1Rp6TjG5lPU63A5HET7c9CwvEOxNOl+XYUcWAct685vDdFn+MoArZsqSyNBfldVQj8thbc21LC2rUiIhedTMsLeX7C7mZurZPe5emexDKPNXqNJUO86e8Q4pIcA5MgccNy3Wu+pwGMkEBHn1+P09uYZg2tPd3qzMsVY1IigrZNcOtZZ5ctu9TjkvlmsouIjVsw1FhIDwmkEn98oYerPIIgMxd2ySmdRMzlM+v/Ontqaw8qCYJiI+JAipIwtBR8p0YIqPCJqZ4nKJF3bG4U6e0p/6GBogmF7/ANOJMm8R8l1w1k7KQY7Y/qIGvO3rBPjFKfspH7DiRkEl8hu0cpCeaaXb6oGGnxAl5YQU09LD4JDqVb/aEzLX7MQpd6pkD0Ggi8LevOTTwRcPRbEN/tGzS6zaowqssMy3h/dxF7BiLpZ2uCZLMxT9A3ZlDYyUN8tPvvHRsUU520XrUiIhedTMsLeX7C7mZurZA+FQWJae/rikgDBj3SlDtNU49DjzSHb2qUnP9uIv91UfRWBRaP6/WrD0Rb6YNYr2RbyARdKfQ8es7OlgQlDJTE3ysZhSaU4mLxvxYyUirYG+18ZxbSYNylEAkb/OonKoa/8bsNm+9W0eZM4uM91NtmauSodmdO+cGadFw6133KSt5432MX1ZKQ2SrrFwpaW0RCoVI4MWGgl+NwFR9/tvQEZZfoowCXvo7orSAPr1HON0zM9tMivx43EMkLeqEpAkElpOPYdV8TYxArvbpfuoBaQqDQwtb7MQ7URJvewv6WN7C1Qx2B6LQo2Ijm3xpCXucG9as9kZ8cS1A6yIS4seGQkkGJpSZlMXKdHsEGnvteE"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19031","langCode":"vi","question":"x7PsKkJPCU8+FwiC802BGvB1f7DTy6u3nzb6s5C1cLkcoE43gJC6/wP3IXPGNhMjCHVDwHmDQMTm5nT2w2yD8HHc3Q362e3V8/S5+qqH3Sw\u003d","answers":["go","would go","could have gone","will go"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEyOh68p0iOdLGZJv3tEcpgT2TZanaiCRtlDpG+gISoWWezj9Yy8fLVKevHruRnmRyw8x1ztJJ/kOKBVMVR5wKpKkofuyvFJhLRj4K8HVS+5b5GMwwfJfMRtsxJcN1yTN84C0CQ55ZvuA0RQrCDuVPg+JgmTI3fQ8ZFWMqOfIGXSIGBz7wy0Q/8TaM6ujktqrhevQmkK0n1RJjApWu1vksf8H0onrOWhQoYUeb6rIz6zZ+cS/ySkIDAC45/fyn45Kx3tFrys2BhlxlERvc7hczDGSdGm6S34/uL/03TZ/iGzLrMcRJdwrMFgAVGiTETccSdNidcsykAJr+aefYN2Brb0wfb/OTWJ9cPvsybgVTaZNd9QyYkZEcfZ9rzNjZUrx2cVY1IigrZNcOtZZ5ctu9TjcNV+3NeKRd0fN5V2ItrAvFCyduhOpL0BSmws89J616NUHBNFKiQVoIAQJ4wyaERN0fE1jZWEnB/ZxnZ00cB9xM0LxcItrXYbA8EwvTe0Snw8h3XQJMierEqo/lu+Mp1Uoe9K+uuXdMfxrMqyDFAAirptwbp9oFP4OU6ywIsfBTlUMOjX9cUPBs9AMfrXcgF04qrHZ77/7mzaTmR40lGAh+cS/ySkIDAC45/fyn45KxzWa3hMYEe1pgPkZQMmuO2WUJomU4B/+vU0IeOzRQ4XNxT+l3rjCDg3n9Ieg4cy4tYx1N4ehJiYxfpCCE4i5fGZ0WTjYIoMkn8qcy8SrK2p4InPaElAiWye+g8/blPG6A0Y8yNeMI3ragVRNqI5ltWGcnQhVOlELpMdX98XE+ZySjkUz2+O3obKGas2QovWYD8Ber64tckenDAtZSWNAu7V1hFLGpaCOMwu0XzsLhJPx6fVzGfizHtnPwRERumcyBSyvs7Hh6ldt/0zMeA7Lp98pL5GqX92Z/QJz92LU5MMvEx78MM94c7A2SjUyW4BqajCe7GTAjAbSRYS81fsDzOr3lvQHIlahAhjPZVUDBOK+6txYu2w8E3QFZemgrvfVqg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19032","langCode":"vi","question":"KZEXweef+WL3SJxsC0Oj8nx+jAASPDcnUFadjVlhjoy/HqJsDclei4GO+lJ2i4NjfIQunqMw7V1ijpPqIQ1D+A\u003d\u003d","answers":["be","would be","will be","would have been"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE24gjl71hT8X4+Owzu39k8sMVr70fG/FxCBCH44nUm2u9SHg0EId6Ilgw8/JM3FyDDv0AT7Qby/oM8pe48wpH82Zft3jwXi67qJGQkSbLqn6dBwkJ9oAtY2iOdWmmqnxiwdjWN11S9iqNU5KKCRa0KvHkbp+QYsmUHtqboy1uIfP/+K7Q7pUWXXhk4nWrpTJ5yNhkPwTRJ4ES/4kOHzuw3pO+L6rxHYymZoIhVw1LFmf/Fw4zdE3jNovDof53XhgZ5xJEyWXpfFkvA043C6NetzC1oTTKBGpE+hh3Q8ABCzp3En3SM787hxa0mj/rMVnoeL0aEInL/UrjsQ1o/3SnXBxtbuaNnnv1vpx6PSGVypin/PuTQxehGIReehX32UAxNNidcsykAJr+aefYN2Brb1bBa9LP1IG7iuWtN0D8IB6Vg3sk8QbD1a0DmOtSzfklh/OUwMKiMVHfwf7H9cAW1zuVVvc/lUtYLPuiY1AszSB8zkxJykrFfXr2PS+7h2GVvbH2P4PhyLUVzpLLscV6+naWBKDOviPhvWBfyrOaoFcKTfMfwCkgj2rhoGBSaKIetx+npHhu7ojXQvDBapoalUzYtyQLI/0cekTCxNbgmLX/Fw4zdE3jNovDof53XhgZ2XjFt+miesoYrfvmmkVS66mj/UBpEVD62EhK7MU/SmB9hPfzOAKWG2cjw47Ns+cYJUqSzFzFuuVVWX+Y8l5g5KqMTqojRSsoZUY3p9ak2nr1g8c/FsYPStWWcZaltKErGarY5gHskt3ZAvN9UOTAQtPpZjqOu3v6LrGLHOYeiwVuy6J2aDIlxECTmAFaytuoFDkFH/K+zlJXsH8azdozq3HnJPOKTezhA+RVZasQBJqpDtaFgnx408fE0I1XFSuCfBBcf/Ge/q1hf5S/RP7ZQc4czystzzGK2zaPZUvaOgoCYlQ3QZSDUxd0blQf0/xoSACBWyorGd15qXeTM1/H4GlHkETOiVSdEs994kovm30tUG3tuTX0mQ78KmmRZu6mVQ/eMM4E55JZjDFd1sg0FQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19033","langCode":"vi","question":"s6dK2VgEDuDBznvDeeVarom++CZJ/Kj+28NBNXir/gJ1wGDQhTLWcL7Uyc9c/8IAyM6FOR5WzgdW5GPFZinlw8kOVh+UWnIfBHrgOhW+oiU\u003d","answers":["had bumped","could bump","should bump","bumped"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE55F8uFeqDQuiElJm1v/z7YtI1W9jMmitUCSXm6dqs2gOrFO7ssj4leprpSr62rBuXWEUsaloI4zC7RfOwuEk/GUkW3l4634+DMZMCcJOEJlWlVf4A7KU34UA3qujcIAHcs1/PbVO26yp1Gc3ZDO9gH/PaygKsmW8CX5fm0ee3BmTSwkAtcWffGiRydyWC2xEq4skNvrJr6BKFB7OruhxZyXdlUxUOg5NGEdbBOqiP49Qxx0LlNscm4cdMDunIq5aB8zACsLIqzn8+hAqoojpnHnxJRB3JtJXSz8M2JbQt/TYCSQczvZ0ZYFLWJRQJkB5GcYU7SiGrQJcoZtshdurJovk6G0x9y/am4OVbIqQiq6yKAZD6zJiK+nqLMJDNjE4N9s46lOU8wUamFi+S+12BOAUx6ADR1hVZrPorrayVcB02T3jzlH8rKwoJjQQGudUmWErljHVi2goCocfXTy+rMLND9zT6tVZN8pshgftTN35xzIzPylvDufF8zs6gcwYISD/zv1F5tqu/yg81uTg1C1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19034","langCode":"vi","question":"DzyBzwF0Q4ReWDs4BYDQbWgq+aekaunj9O3w9dZaVnLARDyxzQZbu+eCN3MDKcvtLkyUtawlMjfZBROejgewB1NOuH6Z0q75iDgL9dmt1H6nRZCmM/kvSi+zzpKxeS7p7PhayR70kqVSCEcrU6GKmQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["had found","found","should ever find","could ever find"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE55F8uFeqDQuiElJm1v/z7ZuTvO0IwTL1VutbAghUyxINz9qiBJAw7RL7bzLKLFqaLKPxpeVCLYzUfwT+NbczOSpIFTsk4DwgR0QkxKAn3ar+472jO9RE5qJRJVAAPVPIbuwayLC/pLkD9oxvIHzYoUQYkKfbn4ApjRAhBu3vdJfib2UmHbDpH8DCaezBvH/umqAbXLy1UY3piXMmAdlhEfdDAzN5FB57Qf4QW3PPXroYCAbW8FA7rSucfcpiJol0wf2K0q65lHkTgV95UDSE+pbIyJBLR8sO3Rmdw4ucgWdtA2qkxNycsB1IXrle6pCBapt+e9KWSlmXAbu4uXtwCAGJ2CKQzNsGQkI/Pml0taKrsu8IlVefM3YfSClFjOIC7oVSsnvACEWUFSVGbChkmofZuxU7Gj10tjJXE/HImai+1oXzXqvD8iH8L7qrdfWmukV0ePjcNyCKD4RDWVpB9zy42dsuuKZrJn3krU0bhdZXdfLk5Ht181eTeJXNZ8UQPo5BonbJQY8DITxtncrb0xKvqQGc0TTtJuvV1Pt3DDXKgXsf/PoCRQwHgOXjafZ1R2c9gMN1/7zaWtc6LRf/tKvDdn/wW/kCbISP7lUh8dlx6XscJ9y0+9VtXJfIdp48sTlIUEKsjRc6wAEdTjY7BMLYt9CQDdJFEHS7TW9wauomUa/Nr1PrwG/z4vjxdDDIzfvJLkBkIixKaCSddn1LFs\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19035","langCode":"vi","question":"U+TNTH05Q+KXIlyPJ65Zd4JG75a5ScDhVQ5l3cA6mWB+2mZ7+BW471jVh/mkToVpNjFisnLdzo5D5WvczZ+flIRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["met","will meet","could meet","had met"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8SE2nWMiQuObuSsdV0XQC2NO8E86mu9oFjYjp9hkLnhp8GkQhN/ujPFFtN1yoEm4oLMYS1Aykj09DmWkZPo8skEIlfgjUkbn5NugHbHT5QnL5OhtMfcv2puDlWyKkIqup+NB7uZ2vahnmctPShDdvl7HKOlJeU3pFBQHUz96zY5Jar3eUWzefT8zPJ8bYwfPrRZ+HHld9+hYOitaBVO5GiikR10wKke0Ot9VW2MXrQjvZBFqYeMJWJlVk5ZTm5odX0oQbBijbo5I4Fv2GS4Stl7snrTJKidOYLVz9wSFJa/2DS4snPUkxHLAbg25lW/y6sB3/zTR+HyA+wwHLo63tWSHnyylmHhNxtpcxLD7/ggOuTrPcCApa8PiRzyFp2cOr2rUdBnGRPTd1qJquzcU22xNz1ajPkIseVg9jOGDqylemo/zc7YtE4Vz5FEMPitUDQ7zw+BiqB3MrPJd9J4p7g2HKleuBNkrfsRjhSUSe+PGt5xAkDR3BYVozKJtsGVR0DcJxKJknm2MspIilrZngtuEu47OW0eoqpCnPtdPZ5Cu264otAfxANoEGhngOWUaaOeRjIuj0ze0D4lZaA+lfs\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19036","langCode":"vi","question":"zwuEfcbjAehQ+hJmqXA+kwonB/eazuWvKF4+qE++0xBk28RvyzQjBGEgq7dhxfa/kSwjNuPz9tgBDe04QqquiQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["stopped","could all stop","had stopped","would all stop"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+Wtyd4AGRlwKdbOZrHOBqLdCcaWH+n3O0JURvegPIajpHO8Ts3Al8q7godPX1/KP83Neax4r/NlAjhTUiP+s0mBY4TF6obII37lI0jCpPqGNs1Fxd8JeYbBmiTg0TlSF231H1S7xwU/k5O3aekfGqn7tu7O8CuArbE++Zh2fdSO9HoGMdJfdTcCvo9gHdfeaJIh1kHKPDx1pyRxmXRXvwyOASQub2pvXUVMKB5TsYcBCrly9MnY2wTEY28ivYk2xkOsppcwGN6SR8xB4uUYLUl7thMfKOUMpDXcPsnkHJEb2nka7OYLzn6O0KfNV30loa/6kFwZVn/bhG4PxUN9houPQ/nPryfLe86zZiFAD5AmeRjTNvhPrNrquKmLh+HHrm92BR3p1oZ9TwKvLqJz30wnjdoLmPVjwmqnD68J78TrxuyzvT6Nb94XgS5QzuFkhgGbiXZOgp6NClIaqMKGyNEhsjW8QpAEdylebg6DEGSlMVeQMKxdeDpawCetfuFa0tPB8XxSAt0SB9PGFJW35RS+oG/UkQ4svIuBEylIIMEg"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19037","langCode":"vi","question":"zGCFGOjdw5vD2yu+zSft6XRyCzub8c3A/SE08jhyjX+5sJKWXJAbjdu65QoYFYXFX8y9lLBB0szR8Afw5D54rw\u003d\u003d","answers":["made","will make","could make","had made"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/eQ1JYuoU3S2WvQSBM3UadILoteyY6kw+cI0Nqt5czHp8GkQhN/ujPFFtN1yoEm4oLMYS1Aykj09DmWkZPo8skEIlfgjUkbn5NugHbHT5QnL5OhtMfcv2puDlWyKkIqup+NB7uZ2vahnmctPShDdvl7HKOlJeU3pFBQHUz96zY5Jar3eUWzefT8zPJ8bYwfPrRZ+HHld9+hYOitaBVO5GiikR10wKke0Ot9VW2MXrQjvZBFqYeMJWJlVk5ZTm5odX0oQbBijbo5I4Fv2GS4Stl7snrTJKidOYLVz9wSFJa/2DS4snPUkxHLAbg25lW/y6sB3/zTR+HyA+wwHLo63tWSHnyylmHhNxtpcxLD7/ggyUZsezPz9qsBh6vBalL/XnB8xac44f3LANp55pTArFCe2Kkswch1AKv3hbvXENb/6Po/jTyDgZxSGKy1A+RjB//fFfPPejRlZUhlqhfJnDllXhbybGueQSxm9WOCd6IvtPRpLD6LvYyq8kQR/SYFgjG2Hd9hEsINm9rR9LzJVlg\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19038","langCode":"vi","question":"tU8motCN2FzWXBh2cjiE6qyrDXGXSt5WvkOUI2dwB/pf2RYp6NJdq1XxI1G5rZ8D","answers":["be","were","am","is"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8G1+oTMiX1dSJkDQnjfpPWKmNHkzu3gX7DbgpglEjzOLIEfkECYBdhHa0lEGHGradaZT8Zxq0fyZMIEeDWYcIq4ZLbxIwSe6DknzahlVHQ1UotKYQhijgx3gYy2UFdLZRWXWcXwXODLWVBSCfIlsJN6TjAiGK9ob4UcGnCvhyL/B/YrSrrmUeROBX3lQNIT6rmFSt/y6859k9D2HYNkuw6eUI6CUSVrCRRAvSROkKWxb5//qC1mIcFfEit7rOZM5D3b9AnoNqOknq1yis/vgVPBKjU1nUCtCMASNESxh3Hn/cUxonfqM5eydpeaLg49+8Ber64tckenDAtZSWNAu7V1hFLGpaCOMwu0XzsLhJPx+JFcX0ejhyc+cjnEIiK/T36LLcul9xfQYF3kMCI7ywtmKMT+0BzGktfXFwUrJqS2vEO08dSFkw1u7NyrnWhW5Nc0ttegBD9C1vpTSQL0FWrG+u572iO4YYslKXtiFbcAE+o+rpkmgIhfrODZggIZAJNICM2ogQJq/kOpFYTGjVcSX20Nxtbc5j/tUcxDHcjh"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19039","langCode":"vi","question":"2IviABZqDvnVNGwZMngR3yZTL5k968bXmEl7npO1doqLjGJyLN1zW2LzKJZfCpYcWsm8/aGekcP6S35iUxxQKQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["were","are","was","had"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwGWlSshmRHRY975kyYOFRpA3yCp65SFTy6e2VmNibHOJ2GruttIa5hja6wL4NppDOEobAWAB5aAtpoGuJ+nO4aWsBUQz04I6rob5RIKYtaRyNuokO75cdj55uGG4O3/Ftt5Rv5mqHfdCbbdxI/GAZF2eGNu6+xzuulieNJp5GM+L4AslFnM7ytb8bAwclJX+wr2v0148b5gCZXktBfv/eQkgtTmMtu2DRyDqe3Rxft706NoaYBU06EjLC/KLFgY4kFsnd7zlqFyHR22UwHU3BzndsxnSOHVEl5/grbKo+7cCgCLB5LJGXMrMoXQ+K4dfkPh4ydG9ctnqDV/p9oWWIILe/XGkVF8eRxXCruPiy6pp8GG5dJiIUJphVv1z0WMnEb5JmNC5cyiwqhn9oZu221tmffurKLZyVA3soDjqDtVIY1WMVHugdbHUrlsSop+h7hTK6KCEl+70eYVRCQ/kIRLbyNcamIdophG9P8WDpHF8uNnbLrimayZ95K1NG4XWV3Xy5OR7dfNXk3iVzWfFEBPa1QF/bNtl45aBqC9KJL/kNEeOQJhkUYkuYssR8fTIF9H9eVzG4vFdCaaFcZ5g78OnK4XOSl6F6YhgJnJitcuHtciHjqPH83xF7fbCqsOxuN/FzuW7aJAz/ptu+tFn70\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19040","langCode":"vi","question":"s89cmCcy36iHZYo2oSYDS1nHSDGxt4k1EVcYRx4eDW4wN/SvYdwIgbtf67wvcQdq","answers":["were","should","is","had"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwyoXJBK9b48YsIcBBbjb6LylD52EYNpIXqYXUMdcmJ2S18TYvTGXeyNnnVQWKcF+bBASslfnowbQK3XGwx79uyal0/bXLcoPa9zF26XVxvfbaMbYq99vQlNld6fT+uXK61IiIXnUzLC3l+wu5mbq2SszLaXrREVlCxdU+9EGF9NJtYcD7bR8ug1E31xTYEko3cGaKAQwIs2bvp/MRpCn3R6FTh6NaksO4eid+L08Z1lZTVGuOOHGTZIwNhhRUQOQ7+zCNvWUSjM61pFkGjSWk6CJbAmA5qjiiwhE5CpM7W7sKEte5FMIMRdNkjCi1ZgwayBUg1PFOa5ES1MvFvOGfRTAy501YhY691p12oNanzysLsqNE5w1ZkNIuLYawdhUJUxaMpSVyC3PGdS8XMH5V7ST/0dQK469w1u+ihphX8BGLg4GlX5HZpDmRZ4ZRpozH3tj9e6L9+J5T17yLWzlwRE/bucu/XIpKvKz2chX8BXpz0dmRx06Cgc1jQDGAEjVtKtR6+LkAfht4G4pdWIvz7qjNMhpESPggdebcDi/eWK6B3oeUhBcKH/SKPcWSxIv/fxg/s4aU77Pw/p6RpSSLudXh31A0pacpFepcku7xZP4FnIm5gppv6uLkWFF9KmEkMIKtwT0PVeFI5jq9TI2pg\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19041","langCode":"vi","question":"OTmUZL7vxl1USCthiChbWcllQFlVLSm5TCf5Wlx9PUFB7s4oJ4rCeZOkYsg2yZdp3NTbZtWoh3Nt8WYXiJxwxl0ioYFk1fz3XIXRBDNA/AQ\u003d","answers":["were","are","was","had"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwGWlSshmRHRY975kyYOFRpA3yCp65SFTy6e2VmNibHOJ2GruttIa5hja6wL4NppDBtYcUTxCy4n6YnuqMzMNM9k4kYL+YOD5HhOzWyyBnOqYLlbeWUOsvQHK+s3jtGZnx+kNZ7I/ynhwo9ydKVfVcrcWAP2v2AYdl1kumgcnxc+Ns1Fxd8JeYbBmiTg0TlSF8NEp27KbZW1GGiAPKq9yB0ofNIWY/rHBgghYirUoVMHPytGacoFGIt5EZ/OXOQaTZwfrsTfAmCJSIDAHQGAA4PwGHcVFuuuenTv2F6b3qlAshVStEiFaMNI2bKVhThnAD7/eYNcsBz7y4UcJIlRSQLXK69WeBjM/nCOny2vxmAN+r/FJkYr5TR0F9cySUrQ8Sa021lVrjo5s1y7nx+TxutkqiwRnZMyTMzRYmyarf3SMcONNhLUb/NmMjY2vMjf/cn2uALIoz6SCGs0ykSilS8Qo3nuHCRHd6tK+mRHogR+pz0dmRx06Cgc1jQDGAEjVtKtR6+LkAfht4G4pdWIvz7vzxiGyHGirB1sFPe6G44uYc5YGl/O89edapDUsXKhJdT3/zo4vrb8iVV+upQhlazIOFwCRNvivm/2hAYyA4P1W950ql45SqIQf0UY64pfcA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19042","langCode":"vi","question":"bFvx9tpMg0YIaiN3EY8Od1ifaQ/Jynp6XsMb71yLFFXeS9OqSvS7rpXRULwSCOYC","answers":["would have come","will come","would come","came"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"bqVGCoyLK5q9ibsxLBG+lpDkaLlJnScgbEj1GBtcZj5ikkJripTZeylvlvuBpw2O03pePwCzpKmia9P0xRv3vpI5pIMVIHt4PX1EgNnSFi8dmRJ0F2Re9FCte6Box50CoMnBWj0BrivgISDvb71UGkrb2F4O8+kdi6EeyhNhMgC78aP52hOXQ1urqR+GikF1j92SVaEAzIg+mhOdsEWK9drGp5087uqvShCsrjgi4zoFvxoBHGhc/WVV0q+1E9pJb9RgXUaf+r56NHspzqQlsY+Y1GUtHYbTpWl2sjbfx+OTm87mHyLBOueDSYdFy3ForHVjtyubSo0Nf0P3zcO6yuwxoua8mO+edWi5BbV/VFmE19UWOYdkEjqW8p1/gYDepz0dmRx06Cgc1jQDGAEjVtKtR6+LkAfht4G4pdWIvz5uv06JIINO61OuIwi893KDqWqBAz9bops/iILJGOwHDYLfso16YrkQUv15mrViXGbj4s5lpyuA09ZO9Ft9kWF4vFn6Uu+o7m3V1b+xTNmry1Pr9YLevUEUxLF/0G50+lMtNrL4Euc8ijBnk6b47tnPP+tIz/HqAZ+22R7M9PhwGJNeaqENN2FI0Y9S7yHt+vq1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19043","langCode":"vi","question":"+QDvMzPda28jyLGFLXc+77PnsQmcjNkMjvuWlIuPc+NF0IuEIbJ/aNT3V9+eFYmb","answers":["if","only if","but for","unless"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzX9hDAFjxIfXUzFsCAvj3xGjyZt2IFDpDzzFPMaSE8b8iZCcMslfTwRv2MpstKjW8bScrfnACw9vX/awnuCXWH9csq7vHF+3CWWAwG5pz+wNYbdnWACjzmD1CCdGi+x0Jlnpum2BEfJxfJi43gHy8qrhb19A21LwTrc52tm/Zccde1aTC4hdVG4NVc9D0cfExSGyDZqYlPSf75GPT4TWzasaustuZ3eIVgQwkmZLuBiSZbPy0E+JEHYUxI/JyN/YPARlujQz/nDp30vsxTzS80EXuymHGlSsx02RBJ3AyCsmezGrgOhrHhiY/bYhdYxGxfCADv50+VEriJZwDxnvD3p+S19ZEnOhkPhLoexlzC1xzboSxlEzPm2MeeAALYRBeV5wH7HapJvJ3K0HebKNv59AuVFUCaiPFQKCzLSzy/ATWltlXzQToDuAgPuKVdE7C/gsXGM2ZCtVSpao9myV/8FvxoBHGhc/WVV0q+1E9pJSByRY5sc+JtrPMBFs3hWnbUwq1LdhDjwwBULFG3KmeKC/2nLVY2mn+CM2lb53Heg/Fw4zdE3jNovDof53XhgZx+bmOMVNUrejz/7N4H69adEQU4xRoIcX1wpFj+FguV4BBZbaihEL3ksDF9WdXa1C0SDfo7P/aMk4eve6ygDUadHJ3d1Ria2YwefGu3f/kj5QpkyQSGRT16GTyXmHIJxzvU5BTRl1exgcWqd/CHXtaKoIYMuV1ar/sNjcj9GfmU7AlKyX/MyXzktnAPpMAbGnwlQ/7Lzs9P0kQUoTGmFIIRQ5BR/yvs5SV7B/Gs3aM6tx5yTzik3s4QPkVWWrEASav1yyru8cX7cJZYDAbmnP7A1ht2dYAKPOYPUIJ0aL7HQRZafVhiU61EWa/Hwd/CVh9mXHw6Si3P/+KgWsbZtXWTcin4LsDcsrTGMXO7/NWy0"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19044","langCode":"vi","question":"zp41McNxOfG1C6C26fkiQgyt2uEqtCmVLYMomEyPCuZdIqGBZNX891yF0QQzQPwE","answers":["unless","otherwise","if","as long as"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzX9hDAFjxIfXUzFsCAvj3xGjyZt2IFDpDzzFPMaSE8b8iZCcMslfTwRv2MpstKjW8bScrfnACw9vX/awnuCXWHEex90Jshiwray1wJavJG3+m9AG1S28DI6tfmvFe5ol3+4v17VqCnopf4GRdls7xxXQGCzr83s3yoG4EmkWK8ItrrNWHjK3cuHoWKv9pYr2OQwZJL5BlHQIomoXuVXSaWMZGTcC3jIvPNqY/F23hCKBF7sphxpUrMdNkQSdwMgrN4ErpXmvdi9znlJ0tLNSJBQHPpImx9bWSBDeGSyOIlAuJXOc7TebqO1A4GcJTnu5+9IrKCy9H4OeIBq2/OgvaFOUYDzEdEUj59Cyrmvx+rcJy9n5KPb4bOc2OomJlPVXzjcYB4dAg1hyppTijLzZ0s3RfuWftANrskZfpEGRxIS+qYvP+192xMMkIMFXcZuREMn/iqlildGlYJXQKaib7Suf6oOR1nw7MoZUSTqfYL2KPLN2lOLJqPKlOxLJQHGCAMN7WU/tM1tTyZOgQMbp8xNdSRk73fg7wgk1sApkzWoKOObY1g6iV0cWaNBW7iLtKKvC7LWtg3tgDCAdqs//CnGB142e9zGJp0ZjUJzoqPJsttTY9JMr2pFh/NVdCFhR+T7DZHUdDZez+ACSwVtQ8ca2Cj+jEtWrgC/VqJWgAu9mC4AY5okjNeTmFK1zTGBEyVHZfIKzu/NWUXnJ26m72sUKn4mwTfEFgb/4m5tB8nazMqN0bDMj5G/aTU72rAkkG0QpcU70pfdN89woxcdljlMhO6fgPoHVeN4n2ORCJDmni5pxs8eVqBMBu+T7UFbqyt5gZE4x7MdWluzBu+w366SG+vbye47AaqRrJIpJ6rrEdcYLL9H1ClW9HFVeWUXkCPPAGJ62gnoZWAYkx7R1cQ2xbFYLgg+jGGyOTAYACbLyUZsezPz9qsBh6vBalL/XnB8xac44f3LANp55pTArFDTE80TSOiTqr2P7OozYaDN3cKdPQnbxnwB71K+b4Nh0zbHAhaVG9ptqtz5wRTRu9uKZ4mkQIvqgWqXANFfBH9DRUA6mWlE2dw8BeCA2EG00w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19045","langCode":"vi","question":"DXWlWTYDieiU8uKrIY3DFJGeC2bLULA2oFwjGfRjT2j33t9M9V66SapbbETTZ4qFkvLxrp5M+xr1cwOZPrT3Prfj9s7slX7DYgwwQptX7k8\u003d","answers":["otherwise","if","unless","only if"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzX9hDAFjxIfXUzFsCAvj3xGjyZt2IFDpDzzFPMaSE8b8iZCcMslfTwRv2MpstKjW8bScrfnACw9vX/awnuCXWGu2JNoQ/Bcax5qrZZWCV0YCgcNOfel+0dsPP16uzzpXaD+8+j493omA12KgiScl0TwlI3lRY9maikpgGwy6YBd27X01lyIvmSh+E6AoSrvdBm7ElA5/ILWvaCbxEXDeRdJls/LQT4kQdhTEj8nI39g8BGW6NDP+cOnfS+zFPNLzQRe7KYcaVKzHTZEEncDIKzeBK6V5r3Yvc55SdLSzUiQUBz6SJsfW1kgQ3hksjiJQLiVznO03m6jtQOBnCU57ufvSKygsvR+DniAatvzoL2hTlGA8xHRFI+fQsq5r8fq3CcvZ+Sj2+GznNjqJiZT1V843GAeHQINYcqaU4oy82dLN0X7ln7QDa7JGX6RBkcSEvqmLz/tfdsTDJCDBV3GbkRDJ/4qpYpXRpWCV0Cmom+0rn+qDkdZ8OzKGVEk6n2C9ijyzdpTiyajypTsSyUBxggDDe1lP7TNbU8mToEDG6fMTXUkZO934O8IJNbAKZM1qCjjm2NYOoldHFmjQVu4i7Sirwuy1rYN7YAwgHarP/wpxgdeNnvcxiadGY1Cc6KjybLbU2PSTK9qRYfzVXQhYUfk+w2R1HQ2Xs/gAksFbUPHGtgo/oxLVq4Av1aiVoALvZguAGOaJIzXk5hStc0xgRMlR2XyCs7vzVlF5ydupu9rFCp+JsE3xBYG/+JubQfJ2ke1rUDEpxps3BxdJXi11Er1pbBUEkqeoXVJoW6LfNQpxeEz5ddfJtfV/uU4ZUt+VHZXUztRLFXhbKFsrNHtP5pQ84oMBbrbNAchHuPtt3UDySpCSpcwCz6EJpaVnMKT2EwP3VSa/3VZhfN38a+2roX2oOUO1dakA/7gclUqG/NvwLWAdjSvbwOI5nTFY8c9eF6pz+gGB2L/ze9kueu3yFBPQIfKnnB3noHtOg61xLDgzNhMWKoWMAE8K5WDkcScvG6MExTOQcsdD0ZhyEobt8hQrO0X4bRuIlOTx8sI4tRx4dVqh2PGSDFKzqlxhk935fqHdl1GRKwNe2H7jXNVl8M5WVMHX3pzR8EIkM9e/ezx"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19046","langCode":"vi","question":"aV6lZhqEd4fjCYQzlMq6+V6KufSd9Z8VPPmv91B89RVaxEkofe591pXjxw3+KCamK6y9R4Vq2vGOuGcTYme2PQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["but for","unless","otherwise","provided that"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8Y2UxqBt9+p0nphiHiJ8pGkvn3UgFF51alxLkOOwA+swx3/fc8VMsihUq0nzf77WSPB4qB2ysKoXGdeMgLVuHivGX2WzB5iJwDr+fx5JTDkCTr025oVhz8Z0sLZNE20jk4bbzB0UoaGK8ldjnpxMGZK29heDvPpHYuhHsoTYTIAu/Gj+doTl0Nbq6kfhopBddndvbqDS3nLu0mt8Di+Cbvs9imhl2ha3yCggLT5uLbBYcIBwoWmTSAwoNiTyf7J+mW1Wq4WRnZEjPJgp564+ly6quPyYp0mvXz2R4bAaUgO7WeW8Qf0ufVvWYf0f6fWJJhKCHMdDs2ygiV6x00aO1UN47fj6rBIDbx1CIl+BLBmLSS7MGpioPKTbqPTjw1G9qqc0211T3dT6MDmS8suQ/FIRQHVhAW9zO2YpBgiQ/zAK89GwucQkYL+tolWNd0OT624JOLCRJOrDVkJUQ5UFBORsfUoAY80HozdbJJl2ITH9iXyFN66w9sRFewhOx9irPU5BTRl1exgcWqd/CHXtaKoIYMuV1ar/sNjcj9GfmU7AlKyX/MyXzktnAPpMAbGn3ZyHjZvdYOvop236BGMWI9elJ8d4D8tpkpWolIJcFFOST10LzX4/mk8DwwrpVvVIJTLA2iDUGLFwmdGEiKusbUSM6kzTKoY2XAjajG0y2x56UjXWI6OWgQWwFKZ715UEVDkFH/K+zlJXsH8azdozq3HnJPOKTezhA+RVZasQBJqGLnLXVixkr3kVCmiQHM2lR80KHST1z+HqIf5LnbnDZ0iMZourAKljogSRZ2iPpgIJS7DbzyvVijOGlwllj+uT/ffVHTbXI3pWyv8vCE0a0a87hh4qMWX84S+V1zor8elQwgq3BPQ9V4UjmOr1MjamA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19047","langCode":"vi","question":"RaZftd0xq1zczuIPoGrSNo4OZ4zDDZYBdXBRs8x73yWx3gMnoKMyugNABcqBKxMAUuZsi7ArckZJbn77P+GJ0A\u003d\u003d","answers":["but for","otherwise","as long as","if"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE0oLHrvFYI4jvGgt6IcnprLIRJkO2yxx0PIMdkFvl4kx+cS/ySkIDAC45/fyn45Kx8c2kNS528YoDt2ESbXSjIyU9PIraJOz1Ia1xJ4rhoIIt5CmgpebMFPSOPcphLDE3rd36hfRyYRvmydUKGf1cRuxzseGvT1XtyIrMNaPLxxNt6DHVh85QEwHj1Pk2h9dmeODTecwRAwxqRsZbh0Q8PK3Kr8+ctiurY/siHykzO0W2bVY0yQGlk3jVUzsXB0P/MsOgd8wts90mBWIeFAdzuR5A5u6AtKZilS35ayF9zZaJmp7snCs+VqDTEbuTUy7Xjf2XypXSF6EsEcEEYk0lHm+XbZcL9111X/oP8HqcycNeQObugLSmYpUt+Wshfc2WiFYaFhmHIYdTYbjinbuL2Xw5XrQ1vaSYtHfUWrH3y89bsnxX/OAm4fxnr+gPNNNCI2ZgWlE6ldwHQdZ9sDAwbdlsf2uy5USZzUWAnP6wyibq5y6NMVFAm3pOrjG0pdA4UvgPC8poQMdj/013Altb3qCckmgEWPIIaUInn+9qlZQ79OnPgzOTmjepdCDlypfeOCKCsNYg1snAlmKgb88QYIQqFSODFhoJfjcBUff7b0BGWX6KMAl76O6K0gD69RzjZ8TE+nIAUeDHR63RWZ8Qpq8Rgvb6nikZY4AgGprhFzjsVRw48b+UYj5K56RvJXmH2/zhRmp0oef64FbrTywONTk4DspTzqeYo/XEBcOhIja"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19048","langCode":"vi","question":"ZxILORlQCzSJyHcMeH0dP89dGm9Dz9zuOXp526ecHNxa/aDmxNfZlfcSYNkmKluW2r5A+5i3toRivS+Fkexsww\u003d\u003d","answers":["if","unless","only if","otherwise"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwrguciCM++tt5CKxbMN2dO06QvClCJDXynrPdmtEjCh03pePwCzpKmia9P0xRv3vuTurrf8R47tR1MYpgBGznw/hBl9ZAi5E2GIYdpgExcER9+GhlU2hgLrMuydDaxvPG3LToHDdGADJlrKTNzvXeCBgWHcX2iXdAPhb+/s9HosOTzJqOtO7HbfXILjeGpicCbWHA+20fLoNRN9cU2BJKN+2oCcjFS2ZY1TLN251JIplJ3v8DJkf9bm0qFnoFwF6E/k5hFtTTWkpppuTwH/D2MlLsNvPK9WKM4aXCWWP65PIBOqw4n1CyLbuGg0Po9eHxxBus/OH4PTghUWMXcMiE6Pp9UsT1lzQXkodPtocXMseQA5G35wu2zTgX6SUEd3MHtjvTyRSu3C/XsaEic+Oa5M4zC1QXkuKmb+QAAYY+1T0inpbyyK3DMHMPvcMlPb+hIzqTNMqhjZcCNqMbTLbHnpSNdYjo5aBBbAUpnvXlQRUOQUf8r7OUlewfxrN2jOrceck84pN7OED5FVlqxAEmq6b8H9RW7X0r8ULeTEPOUETTmnFMo1Xck7s5hxb5NOfaLRgMhbYoW5Z6YFXOZX56YIxurdaFZNytiI7OYHiwUvYMvmaPOZcUiZpe7INJNN07xdQHF5HhIiUmjFO8H5i3BLJhRc0bhV29a1nR7lw6arvfmZXj942OTNi+T8ndQELg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19049","langCode":"vi","question":"2tfOBSKnamNvdgxky6PM+YqLBZH/WuUHJzoSClEOZI5SLcA0bT/y7+E+CGzV1DsDyX3Y5pbSzPiYMzsyQZZXiQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["otherwise","as long as","but for","unless"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4BO5g+AL0F0j3DePr3xloj2v3sA0zrAjxtM3LTRVrj403pePwCzpKmia9P0xRv3vuTurrf8R47tR1MYpgBGznw/hBl9ZAi5E2GIYdpgExcER9+GhlU2hgLrMuydDaxvPG3LToHDdGADJlrKTNzvXeCBgWHcX2iXdAPhb+/s9Hosq2Amn+PS36BWS5EHcnBwtS+ALJRZzO8rW/GwMHJSV/tFWIpoHRWu5WG69Vzy87RuV3hdUwz0HcYBBfzWc6FaXcjYkSqv3V7uBtIYkH4oRFBqqWBYRed6TMO+2aVtqCGNGQReBCpjrVKv90ECalbkM6JyYgugTLdhlEmvouxacg960u56yxXmRjRDD13d/mC7IhgAP9S2n6o+MM5QORjLX7SmNBTQ8Qftde0pJEFzx+divPmXlwIOQsa/jxIKg0PcsUs05gRM3QfpW4WDKvUG+CRd2xuFOntKf+hgaIJhe/zWMedSY9fcgPaTF8e6UnwLI6jet5mZ1gXuzxIpDdMH4ga/osL2SIpXA0T7UDcH6CbgMLamk1NwzURNNSN2nZ8+5Q5Zh4Yc5QxOsP9lOQX35sEZkZllCbaDSIXy0L9FtldhQ3DWV5BaCs3V1LAF0gVgPG+D1wNreeC/biW6ZnEm3zrk6z3AgKWvD4kc8hadnDq9q1HQZxkT03daiars3FNtBqy85dZ6EhAQlSz6LqPaI/D/avMEmfieC4kxmn+U4uEgXWUwr+nkL8TqUC6YDZczwExOjKGyT1UZFcu9cHwkUg3Y50H4Oo9Lga153Ae2SP2VJbRo/uQRgCtndGDUTKsF"}]